Double dribble.
二次运球
Why, because I'm black?
有吗? 嫌我长得黑吧?
Yeah, that's what I thought.
哼 我就知道
Me?
我?
Ten seconds left. We need a basket.
还剩10秒了 再来一球啊
Play one. Play one.
进一个 进一个
Kurt, Kurt, Kurt. Here.
Kurt Kurt  Kurt 这里
Get in.
送进去
Bring it in!
送进去!
Bank's open, Lenny.
打篮板 Lenny
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
好的 好的!
Yeah.
太好了
Bank's open.
好球
His foot was on the line.
他踩线了
First off, I'd like to thank the Earnshaw family...
首先 我要感谢Earnshaw一家
...for lending us their beautiful lake house to help us celebrate our victory.
把这美丽的湖畔别墅借给我们 庆祝胜利
Yeah, the Ferdinando Five.
Ferdinando 五虎!
They're dynamite.
他们最棒了
You're drunk, Dad.
你喝多了 爸爸
Yeah.
是嘛
Hey. We're here to celebrate the kids' shots, not your shots.
我们是为孩子们庆祝 不是你
Anyway, I wanna talk about what you kids did this afternoon.
不管怎样 我得说说孩子们下午的比赛
You know, you played the game just like I always ask you to.
知道吗 你们的表现令我非常满意
You left everything you had out there on that court.
因为你们全力以赴的比赛
So that when the final buzzer went off...
所以当终场哨音响起的时候...
...you were champions.
冠军就属于你们了
Now, I want you to promise me something.
现在 我要你们答应我
I want you to play life just like you played that game today.
我要你们像今天的比赛一样 去追求你们的生活
So when that final buzzer of life goes off...
这样在人生的终场哨音响起之时
...you'll have no regrets.
你们将心安无憾
Here's to coach.
敬教练
You're my first champions. My first champions.
你们是我的第一支冠军队
Stick together.
你们要团结
- Time to die. - No.
- 死期到了 - 不要
Murder.
绝杀
I am the biggest agent in Hollywood and you just pissed me off.
我可是好莱坞最大牌经纪人 而你敢把我惹毛了
And now I'll pull Brad Pitt from your movie.
我要让布拉德皮特退出你的电影
I'll pull Julia Roberts from your movie. I don't care, Sandy.
还有茱莉亚罗伯茨 我才不管 Sandy
That's right, you better back down.
这才对 你最好让步
Thank you.
谢谢
Have a good Fourth of July. All right, love you too.
独立日快乐 好了 我也爱你
What's up, boys? Hey.
嘿 孩子们
Greggie, Keithie.
Greggie Keithie
You guys ever hear of a game called Chutes and Ladders?
你们有没玩过 滑坡与梯子?
Pretty awesome game.
非常棒的游戏
I used to play it when I was a kid.
我小时候就玩这个
Okay, what it is, is they give you a spinner.
你会拿到一个转盘
And you spin. If you land on a ladder, you get to climb up the ladder.
如果转到梯子 你就可以爬上去
If you land on a chute, you slide down the chute and start over again.
如果转到滑梯 你就得滑下来重头开始
Yeah, and what happens? The winner gets a training bra?
那又怎样? 赢了奖励个小胸罩?
Yeah, Dad, that game sounds like it sucks.
爸 那游戏听起来逊毙了
I'm telling you, this was the greatest game.
告诉你们 这游戏非常好玩
Me and my buddies would play it.
我和兄弟们会在冬天
We'd go down in the basement, drink hot chocolate.
跑到地下室 倒杯热可可 玩上一整天
I wouldn't mind a hot chocolate right now.
我现在可顾不上热可可
Hey, Rita.
Rita
Dude, you gotta text her. She's doing laundry.
伙计 你得给她发信息 她在洗衣服
Hey, Dad, we were at the Spielbergs' house yesterday.
对了 爸 我们昨天去了斯皮尔伯格家
They have a 150-inch TV. Can we get one of those?
他家有台150英寸的电视 我们能不能也买一台?
When you direct E. T. I'll get you one of those.
等你导演了"ET"我就给你买
- Beg for mercy. - What is the object here? I don't get it.
- 求你放了我 - 这游戏到底要干什么?
You're on a cruise ship and you chop people's heads off with a chain saw?
跑游轮上 用链锯砍其他人的头?
Oh, and you can drown them.
你还可以淹死他们
Oh, you can drown them. Now I get it.
还能淹死他们 我明白了
Granny overboard.
老奶奶坠船了 (加200分)
Can somebody answer the phone?
有人能接下电话吗?
Maybe I should get some chamomile for my throat too.
也许我也该弄点甘菊润润嗓子
Stop texting the nanny. You know how gross that is...
别给保姆发短信了 你不觉得一个孩子
...for a kid to text his nanny? Just go down the hallway.
给保姆发短信很恶心吗? 自己去走廊叫
Why? You text everybody.
为什么? 你给其他人也发短信的
I text people for my job so I can make money to pay for your texting.
我给人发短信是为了工作 才能挣钱付你们的短信费
- Okay, I got everything for you, boys. - Who was that on the phone, Rita?
- 孩子们 你们要的我都拿来了 - 谁的电话 Rita?
I'm sorry, Mr. Feder, I don't know. Becky answered.
对不起Feder先生 我不知道 Becky接的
- Okay, okay. Thanks for making that. - Oh, my God, Rita.
- 好了 谢谢你做的 - 天哪 Rita
This isn't Godiva. What are you, trying to poison me?
这不是Godiva的 你是在下毒吗? (全球最精致的手工巧克力公司)
Good Lord, go back to texting.
天哪 你们还是发短信吧
I don't ever wanna hear that out loud again.
我可不想听你们大吼大叫了
What the heck's going on out here?
外面什么情况?
Oh, my God.
天哪
I didn't mean to. It was an accident.
我不是故意的 这是意外
I don't care. Are you all right? What the heck were you doing?
别管它 你没事吧? 你在干什么啊?
I was trying to use the Navy.
我在试着用导舟
The Navy? What's the Navy?
导舟? 什么导舟啊?
The Navy in the car to ask it a question.
车里的导舟 可以问他问题
You mean the navigation system, idiot.
你说的是导航仪 笨蛋
- Keithie, relax. - Some man called.
- Keithie 别说了 - 有人给你打电话
He said your friend, Coach Buzzer, went to heaven.
他说你的朋友 哨音教练去天堂了
I was trying to find heaven for you on the Navy station...
我在用导舟帮你找天堂
...so you could go visit him.
这样你就可以去看他了
Who's your friend, Dad?
你那朋友是谁啊 爸爸?
Coach Buzzer was someone very special in Daddy's life.
哨音教练是爸爸生命中 非常特别的一个人
It's terrible.
太糟糕了
Okay, go drink some hot chocolate with these guys.
和他们进屋去喝点热可可吧
You sure you're okay?
你真没事吧?
Okay, sweetie.
好 亲爱的
You're splashing your brother.
你洒到你弟弟了
Eric, hon? It's your mom.
Eric 亲爱的 你妈妈的电话
Oh, my God. Eric. Are you all right?
天哪 Eric 你没事吧?
Donna.
Donna
Oh, my God, Bean. Bean, stay on the duck.
天哪 Bean 呆在小鸭子上
Stay on the duck. What is happening?
发生什么了?
Oh, hon.
天哪 亲爱的
Hello, Mommy.
你好 妈妈
- Hey. - Hey, Mom.
- 你好 - 你好 妈妈
Hi, Mom.
你好 妈妈
Well, I'll see you there. All right.
好的 过去再说
Hey, is something wrong?
出了什么事?
Yeah, it'll be all right. I'll talk to you about it later.
没事的 我等下和你说
I made the pumpkin risotto that we saw...
我做了意大利南瓜饭
...on Rachael Ray's "Seasons of Summer" special.
和Rachael Ray 夏季特别节目上的一样噢
- It's awful, Mom. - It tastes like roadkill.
- 烂透了 妈妈 - 味道就像被撞死的动物
Deanne, do you hear how they talk to me? Do you hear how...?
Deanne 你听到他们怎么 对我说话的吗?
You gotta say something.
你得说说他们
All right, kids. Now, you know your father works very hard...
好了 孩子们 你们爸爸要打扫房子
...at keeping this house clean and putting meals on the table for us.
还要为我们做吃的 非常辛苦
Hello?
而你们呢?
Besides...
除此之外
...I brought us a pizza.
我买了个披萨
You know what? Fine.
知道吗? 好吧
Have your pizza. Have your pizza.
吃你们披萨 吃你们披萨
You broke my heart.
你们伤了我的心
Looks like it's his time of the month again.
他每个月的那时候又来了
God, that's rough, buddy.
天哪 那真痛苦啊 伙计
Who's making the funeral arrangements?
谁在筹备葬礼?
Oh, his niece? She must be devastated.
他的侄女? 她肯定心力交瘁了
Hey, is she still hot, do you know?
她还是那么性感吗?
Don't make me lose my temper, Marcus.
别把我惹火了 Marcus
What?
什么?
Hey, if I don't make it to the funeral...
如果我最后没能出席葬礼
...tell the police it was Arlene from Applebee's.
告诉警察是Applebee餐厅的Arlene干的
No, thanks for calling me.
谢谢你通知我
And I'll see you there.
到时候见
Bye.
再见
The coach is dead.
教练去世了
His funeral is this Friday.
葬礼在星期五
I don't think I can handle this alone.
我恐怕一个人扛不住
Can you come with me?
你能陪我一起去吗?
Of course.
当然可以
I'll postpone my cataract surgery.
我会推迟白内障手术的
You are my special lady.
你是我的女神
Now I'm gonna transport you to a world of serene relaxation.
现在我要带你进入一个 平静祥和的世界
Okay, guys, let's try to act normal in there.
好了 伙计们 让我们表现的正常点
What's wrong with your sunglasses?
为什么不戴太阳镜了?
I don't want any reason for these guys to call me...
我可不想有机会让他们叫我
Hollywood!
好莱坞!
- Hey. Look at that. Kurt McKenzie. - Hey.
- 嘿 看看是谁啊 Kurt McKenzie - 嘿
- And the whole McKenzie clan. - Come here, man.
- 还有McKenzie全家 - 你好
- Deanne, you look great. - I do?
- Deanne 你看起来不错 - 是嘛?
My wife's over there. Go and say hi. Children.
我妻子在那儿 去打个招呼吧 孩子们好
I see that ass is still growing.
你屁股又长大了
Got a little Kardashian in there.
我们多了个小Kardashian (美国性感人物)
Well, you've kind of turned into a little Michael Vick thing, if he was bulimic.
你快变成小号的Michael Vick了 如果他也够贪吃的话
Hi, Roxanne.
你好 Roxanne
I don't know if you remember me. I was at your wedding.
还记得我吗 我参加过你的婚礼
I was the one that was table dancing all night. Deanne McKenzie.
我就是整晚在桌子上跳舞的那个 我叫Deanne McKenzie
Of course.
当然
- Deanne, hello. - Hi, good to see you.
- Deanne 你好 - 见到你真好
Oh, my God, you're glowing.
你看上去容光焕发
You look so beautiful with your pregnancy.
怀孕了还这么漂亮
What the hell are you talking about?
你他妈说什么呢?
I'm just playing.
我开玩笑的
Oh, my God. You should see your face. You were like, "Huh?"
看你那表情 "怎么了?"
Little Lenny Feder.
小小Lenny Feder
Mama Ronzoni got big, huh?
Ronzoni妈妈又胖了?
Look at this handsome hunk of prosciutto.
看看这个大帅哥
And such a big success.
这个大人物
Come on, give Mama a kiss.
来给妈妈亲一下
Can I get a...? Can I get a cheek at all?
能...? 能亲到脸颊吗?
I got you, I got you. Poked in the eye by the hat, but I'm all right.
我亲到了 虽然眼睛被帽子戳了一下 不过没事
How about your son-in-law here, I hear he's a house husband now.
你女婿怎么了 据说变家庭煮夫了
My daughter's gotta bust her hump all day to pay the bills...
我女儿每天拼死拼活赚钱付账单
...while dummy here stays home and cleans.
而那个蠢蛋却在家打扫卫生
I don't know how you could talk to me like that...
你凭什么这样说我
...when you look like Idi Amin with a propeller on your head.
你自己都是个头顶螺旋桨的傻子
- That's nice that he could... - Roxanne, this is my mother.
- 幸好他还能... - Roxanne 这是我母亲
Hello, Mama Ronzoni, I'm so pleased to meet you. I'm Little Lenny's wife.
你好 Ronzoni妈妈 很高兴见到你 我是小Lenny的妻子
What a spicy quesadilla you got yourself, Lenny.
是个墨西哥大美女啊 真有你的 Lenny
Yeah, she tastes great.
是呀 她很赞的
I bet.
我想也是
Didn't I tell you to turn the phone off there, Greg?
我不是说过来这要关手机的吗 Greg?
Yeah, but it's my massage therapist.
但这是我的按摩理疗师
What? No, no. No cell phones.
什么? 不 不行 不准打手机
No cell phones? Then I'm out of here.
不能打手机? 那我走了哦
Higgie.
Higgie
Who's ready to get their funeral on?
谁准备好葬礼了?
I'm sorry, death makes me weird.
抱歉 死亡让我变得很奇怪
What's up, McKenzie?
你好呀 McKenzie
You got those soft hands. Still using Palmolive?
手真软 还在用Palmolive? (棕榄，1928年收购了高露洁)
Hey, what's up, Lenny?
最近怎样 Lenny?
Buddy, I thought you were gonna start working out.
兄弟 我以为你有在健身呢
- What does that mean? - You're fat.
- 什么意思? - 你发福了
No. No.
没有
Hey, guys, this is good news. I always wanted to represent you.
嘿 有个好事我一直想问你
You're the third Olsen twin?
你是Olsen Twins的老三吗? (美国著名美女姐妹艺人)
Keep it down. Hey, so these are your kids?
别闹了 这是你的孩子们吗?
And who's that girl? That's not a nanny, is it?
那个女孩是谁? 不会是保姆吧?
No, no, this is a friend of ours from China.
不 不 这是我们的一个中国朋友
Oh, yeah. No, I've been on that website.
是嘛 我也上那个网站
No, no, no.
不 不不
Like an exchange student that... My wife brought her into the house.
她是交换生... 我老婆带回来的
Oh, your wife's into chicks. Oh, that's nice.
你老婆喜欢小妞啊 那太棒了
Hollywood. See, he always lucks out.
好莱坞 他总是这么幸运
- Just an exchange student. - I always thought...
- 她只是个交换生 - 我一直以为...
Hey, now.
伙计们
Lamonsoff. Rolling up in a Caddy?
Lamonsoff 混上凯迪拉克了?
That's how we do it.
这就是我们的生活
And you, you've grown up on me, man. Are you a B-cup now?
看看你 长大了啊 现在用B罩杯啦?
Hey, nice ears. You get the NFL package on those?
耳朵长得不错 靠它们拿到橄榄球联盟套票的?
Nice Caddy. You selling lawn furniture and crack?
凯迪拉克真帅 你在卖草坪家具和毒品吗?
Come on, I'm the co-owner of Branchville Lawn Furniture, man.
我可是Branchville草坪家具 的合伙人
I'm the boss now, baby.
我现在是老板了
Oh, good for you, Eric.
真不错 Eric
- Glad you brought your mother. - Oh, that's a good one.
- 很高兴能带你妈来了 - 这玩笑不错
It's like shaking hands with an Eagle. I'll see you later.
感觉像和老鹰握手 一会儿见
Oh, my God. It's Captain Caring of the SS Melodrama.
天哪 那是唱诗班里的Caring主唱
Oh, he's gonna play this one big.
他要大显身手了
Cue "Hey."
说"嘿"
Hey.
嘿
- Hell of a circumstance, huh? - I know, I know. It sucks.
- 气氛真伤感? - 我知道 我知道 很伤心
Great to see you.
见到你真好
Well, the Buzzer's up there coaching heaven's team now.
哨音在上面训练他的天堂之队去了
- That's true. - He's got Wilt, Pistol Pete, Dr. J.
- 是啊 - 有Wilt Pistol Pete Dr.J.
Yeah, Dr. J's alive still.
Dr. J.还活着
- Well, those type of guys. - Yeah, yeah.
- 反正像他那样的 - 是啊
You look good, though, man.
你看起来气色不错
It's like if Elvis was an Oompa Loompa...
像是小矮人版的猫王
Well, I don't make jokes at funerals because it's disrespectful.
我不在葬礼上开玩笑 太失礼了
But if that's part of your healing process, I'm cool with it.
但如果这样能让你不那么伤心 我就不介意
That's nice. Thanks.
你真好 谢谢
Are you cool with a finger in you?
你介意我用手指头插你么?
Hey, Roxanne.
Roxanne
Remember Rob, the guy I always tell you about? Rob?
记得Rob吗 我总和你提起的? Rob?
Of course.
当然
The kid who didn't hit puberty till he was 19, right?
19岁才进入青春期的那孩子?
That was our secret.
那是我们的秘密
And this must be your mother.
这位一定是你妈妈
My wife.
我妻子
I'm sorry.
抱歉
Hi. I'm Gloria.
你好 我是Gloria
Oh, it's so nice to meet you. Your design line is so beautiful.
很高兴见到你 你的衣着设计很漂亮
Oh, thank you, thank you.
谢谢你
- And I love your scarves. - Thank you.
- 我喜欢你的 围巾 - 谢谢你
She'll be tying me up with those later.
她过会儿要用它把我捆起来
He's not kidding.
他不是开玩笑
Oh, grody.
哦 恶心
Oh, those are long, long tongues.
你们舌头真长
We'll see you in there. See you in there.
我们里头见 里头见
Hi, guys. Right over there? Yep.
你们好 那里吗? 是的
Sit right here, sit right here. I'm gonna go say hi to Lenny.
坐这里 坐这里 我要去和Lenny问好
- No, honey. - Oh, hi. Lenny.
- 不 亲爱的 - 你好 Lenny
How you doing?
你好吗?
I heard through a little bird...
我听人说
...that you guys rented the Earnshaw lake house for us...
你们租了Earnshaw湖畔别墅
...for the entire weekend.
给大家过周末
That's like a dream come true for us.
这就好像梦想成真
We had to rent it for the whole weekend be...
我们租整个周末 是因为...
We don't get to stay the whole weekend. We have to go to Milan.
但我们不会一直呆在那里 因为我们明天得去米兰
For Roxanne's fashion show.
Roxanne有个时装秀
Oh, my God, that's a shame.
天哪 多可惜啊
Oh, but you're gonna have so much fun in Milan.
但你们在米兰会玩的很开心的
You know, J Lo and Marc Anthony vacationed there last year.
詹妮弗・洛佩兹和马克・安东尼 去年就在那渡假的
It's up the street from Lake Como, where George Clooney has a villa.
就在Lake Como的那条街上 乔治・克鲁尼的别墅旁边
I read too many of those magazines.
我八卦杂志看太多啦
- No. - Come on. I'm sorry.
- 不 - 来吧 抱歉
- He hates when I talk about this. - We'll just...
- 他讨厌我谈论这个 - 我们只是...
We are backing away. Ashamed, right?
我们回去了 真不好意思 是不是?
Oh, and Tom Cruise got married there too.
对了 汤姆・克鲁斯也在那儿结婚的
- Thanks for letting me know. - What?
- 谢谢你告诉我 - 什么?
Well, I don't understand why you had to rent it for a whole weekend.
我不明白你为什么必须租整个周末
Because it's a holiday. They won't rent it to you for one night.
因为是假期 单独一晚人家不租给你
So your friends are partying all weekend while you're stuck in Milan.
那当你困在沉闷的米兰时 你朋友们可以狂欢了
- Yeah. - That was nice of you.
- 是啊 - 你真是贴心啊
It was nice of us. It's your money too, isn't it?
应该说我们俩很贴心 也是你的钱吧?
Yeah, it's your money, it's his money, it's my money.
是啊 是你的钱 也是他的 还是我的
Let's put all our cash in a pile and split it.
我们把钱混一起然后分了吧
That's a nice hat, it brings out the death in the room.
不错的帽子 给房间里带来生气
I'm sorry, I'm nervous. And it's a funeral, I get weird.
抱歉 我很紧张 葬礼搞得我怪怪的
There he is, Joe Hollywood.
他在那儿 好莱坞
Mr. Big Shot Agent.
大牌经纪人
You think he represents Hulk Hogan?
你觉得他能代表Hulk Hogan吗? (美国八、九十年代的摔角偶像)
No way.
不可能
Then he ain't that big, is he?
那他也没那么大牌吧?
By the way, if anyone asks, Rita is an exchange student.
顺便说下 有人问的话就说Rita是个交换生
Andre.
Andre
I think I just sat on your adding machine.
我想我坐在你的计算器上了
Now I know what happened to the fish tank.
现在我知道鱼缸是怎么回事了
Coach Robert "The Buzzer" Ferdinando...
Robert教练 人称哨音Ferdinando
...was a caretaker by profession.
是一个守护者
What a wonderful word to describe his devotion to his fellow man.
这是多么美好的一个词 来总结他毕生的贡献
He truly took care.
他全力以赴的去守护
When Robert knew that his time was short...
当Robert知道他时日不多时
...he told me there was one specific man he wanted...
他告诉我 他想让一个人
...to say a few words to memorialize him.
说几句话 来悼念他
So I'd like to ask Lenny Feder to come up now.
请Lenny Feder上台吧
I'm sorry, I'm not prepared at all.
抱歉 我完全没有准备
I feel very honored...
教练让我上来讲话
...that coach asked me to do this, but...
我感到很荣幸 可是
I also feel terrible because I haven't seen the coach in so long.
同时也感到很内疚 因为我已经很久没来看望他了
And he always wanted me to come to town and see him...
他一直希望我能来这里见见他
...and I got caught up in what I've been doing and I regret it.
但我总是忙于自己的事 抽不开身 我感到很后悔
I understand that the St. Mark's team of 1978...
我知道1978年的St. Mark队
...was the only championship team that the coach ever had...
是教练的唯一一支冠军队
...and that's very impressive, I gotta say...
就我们当时的资质而言
...judging from the talent we had to offer.
确实令人印象深刻
I mean, believe it or not...
信不信由你们
...Robbie and Marcus were actually shorter back in 1978.
1978年Robbie和Marcus比现在还矮
But those guys had a skill you never mastered.
但他们掌握了一项你从没学会的技巧
They knew how to pass the ball.
他们懂得传球
Looks like somebody has to learn how to pass the Kentucky Fried Chicken.
看来某人得学学把炸鸡传给别人
I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
开玩笑的
We're saying goodbye to a big part of our lives. All of us.
我们五个已经过完了生命的大部分
You affected everybody in this room.
你影响了在场的每一个人
And I hope we get to live our lives like you.
希望我们能有像你一样的人生
Have no regrets when life's final buzzer sounds.
在生命的终场铃声响起时 心安无憾
So let's all bow our heads in silence.
让我们为他默哀
They should have just ended it right after you.
你讲完 就该结束的
This is insanity.
这太蠢了
Yeah.
是的
Five bucks it takes him down on one knee.
五块钱赌他会单腿跪下
You're on.
好啊
Stop it.
别那样
Grow up, will you?
你长不大吗?
Oh, look at him now.
噢 看看他
Don't get so mad there, Robbie.
别这么生气嘛 Robbie
So how we feeling about Rob's girl? We're happy for him, or...?
Rob女朋友如何? 我们该为他高兴还是...
Oh, my God. The St. Pauli Grandma? She seems all right.
噢 天 那个德国大妈? 她看起来还行
She's pretty.
她挺可爱的
You know, in a "me in a wig" sort of way.
有点... 我爱戴假发 的感觉
Yeah. Yeah, exactly.
对 就是
When Ben Franklin was flying that kite and it had the key on it...
富兰克林绑在风筝上 吸引闪电的那把钥匙
...that was to her apartment.
就是她家的
Oh, that was good, man.
啊 太对了
You know, but I gotta say, he seems like he's in love, you know?
但我不得不说 他看上去是真心的
He was in love with the first three wives.
他对他前三任老婆都是真心的
The Cheater, the Beater and the Eater.
一个骗子 一个暴力妹和一个暴食女
You know, his problem is he's always so overly in love so quick, you know?
他的问题在于每次都 太快陷入爱河而无法自拔
And then one day he snaps and then it gets ugly in a hurry.
然后某天他一发飙就把一切都搅黄了
Coffee, Mr. Feder?
您的咖啡 Feder先生
No, no, no. I'm good, I'm good.
啊 不 不用 我很好
I mean, thank you. That's cool of you to voluntarily wanna give me coffee.
我是说 谢谢 你真好 自愿给我端杯咖啡
Just, you drink it, you know, while you're studying inside the church.
你自己喝 在教堂里学习时喝掉吧
But you texted me you want coffee.
但您给我发短信 说要喝咖啡
I texted you that I wanted you to drink the coffee and study.
我是说让你喝咖啡并学习
So study your books in the church.
去教堂里念你的书吧
Go ahead. All right, Rita.
去吧Rita 没事
Fast food? You guys eat the fast...?
快餐? 你们吃不吃...
Mommy, I want some milk.
妈妈我想喝奶
Oh, sure, angel. You come here. I'll give you a little something.
噢 没问题 宝贝儿 来吧 妈妈喂你点
Slow down, honey. Not such big gulps.
慢点 亲爱的 别这么大口吞
You're gonna get a tummy ache.
待会儿要肚子痛的
- Your son is so cute. - Yeah.
- 你儿子真可爱 - 嗯
How old is he?
他多大了?
Oh, he's 48 months.
呃 他... 48个月了
That's 4.
4岁了
Yeah.
是
We meant to stop last year, but he likes it so much...
去年打算断奶的 但他太爱吃了
...and we don't like to say no.
我们也不忍心拒绝
Hey, sweetheart?
嘿 甜心?
Could you use a fork, please?
请你用叉子吃好么?
No.
不行
No, no, no!
不 不 不行!
Looks like she didn't get the memo.
看来她缺母爱
- Hey. Let me get that spot. - Hey, gotta respect the Caddy.
- 嘿 那是我的点 - 嘿 这可是凯迪拉克
It's nice you drove your piggy bank here.
真好 把你的小猪存钱罐开来了
- Hey.
- 嘿
Hey. Hi, Gloria.
嗨 Gloria
- Look at this. - Come on.
- 看这里 - 来吧
Yeah.
好的
Hey, Rob's car is an Oompa Loompa too.
哈 Rob人可爱车也可爱
- Okay, watch the edge. - It's cute. It'll do for one night.
- 好的 当心脚下 - 地方还不错 住一晚没问题
Yeah? You can handle it?
是吗? 你可以吗?
Daddy, what is that machine doing?
爸爸 那台机器在干嘛?
It's getting rid of the moths, honey.
它在赶蛾子 宝贝
Where's it taking them?
把它们赶到哪儿去?
- Hell. - Don't say that, Higgins.
- 地狱 - Higgins 别这么说
I'm sorry. Not hell, Mexico.
抱歉 不是地狱 是墨西哥
No, it's giving them electricity...
不 是对它们放电
...so the moths fall asleep electrically.
然后那些蛾子就被电睡着了
It's electrocuting them?
这是电刑吗?
- No, no, no. - But, Daddy, they're dying.
- 不 不是 - 可是爸爸 它们会死!
- It's killing them? - No.
- 是在杀死它们? - 不是
Daddy, no.
爸爸 不
No, no, it's not.
不 不 没死
Okay? Let me adjust it.
我来证明它没死 好吗?
Look, they're all all right, I promise you.
它们都没事 我保证
See? Look at this guy.
瞧 看看这家伙
He's still sleeping.
他还没睡醒
It's dead, Dad.
老爸 它死了
A porch swing.
噢 一个门廊秋千
I know what I'm doing this weekend.
这个周末有事做了
Now he's dead.
现在他死了
Welcome back to 1978, everybody. The lake house.
各位 欢迎回到1978年的湖畔别墅
Nothing's changed, it's unbelievable.
一切都没变 真难以置信
I don't remember this big.
我记得没这么大啊
This is my kitchen. This is it, right now.
这是我的厨房 就是它了
Oh, please, enough with the kitchen.
噢 够了 别再提厨房了
Why you so mean?
什么意思?
We could've done this.
我们可以这么干
- An organ. - Oh, my God, look at this kitchen.
- 一架风琴 - 噢我的天 瞧这厨房
- That's enough, already. - Could you at least humor me?
- 够了 - 你就不能哄哄我吗?
Is this like an Outward Bound thing?
这是拓展训练营之类的地方么?
I mean, it's like an episode of Lost.
这里很像"迷失"里的场景
Hon, you might not wanna bang on that.
宝贝 别这么锤琴
But I like playing it like this.
我喜欢这么玩
Okay. Okay.
行了 行了
So listen, guys, who's getting what room?
好了 大家听着 房间怎么分?
Actually, I made a map of who gets which room.
实际上我给各位做了张房间表
I took the liberty of reserving the room with the waterbed...
我预留了有水垫床的房间
...for Gloria and myself.
给Gloria和我自己
You're gonna do the backstroke tonight.
你今晚要仰泳式啊
I wanna go swimming with you guys tonight.
我今晚也要跟你们一起游泳
Oh, honey, we're not really going swimming. What I meant was...
哦 亲爱的 我的意思 不是真的游泳 而是
That's okay. She doesn't need to know what you mean.
行了 她不需要知道什么意思
- I don't even know what you mean. - Oh, I know what she meant.
- 我都不知道你什么意思 - 噢我知道她什么意思
Anyway, let's get back to the room picking.
回到选房间的话题来
Rob, would you like to take us on a tour?
Rob 你愿意带我们参观一下么?
I'd love to show you a tour. Gloria was just trying to be cool.
我很愿意带你们四处看看 Gloria只是照顾气氛
I need someplace near a bathroom.
我要离厕所近的房间
Why does the grandma get to go swimming and I don't?
为什么老太婆能去游泳而我不能?
Let's go, let's go.
走吧 走吧
Okay, here's the big daddy.
好嘞 这里是最好的房间
The master bedroom.
这房子的主卧
You know what? Lenny should have that. Lenny should have that.
这间房得让Lenny住
- Oh, no, no, no. - I agree.
- 噢 不 不 - 我同意
Honey. Honey. Come on, let the kids have it.
亲爱的 回来 让孩子们用这间房吧
It's a fun time for the kids to be together and they can do kids' things.
让这些孩子们呆在一起 干点孩子们的事 会比较有趣
Come on, go share it. Share the master bedroom.
去吧 你们共享这间主卧
Kids win.
孩子们赢了
Yeah. Yeah. Don't you think?
是的 你也这么想吧?
Yeah, okay.
是的
- Cool.
- 酷
Hey, Dad.
嘿 老爸
What's the big box attached to the back of the TV?
电视后面连着的大盒子是什么?
That's the rest of the TV.
那是电视的后半部分
They didn't always have flat screens there, sport.
这里并不都是平板电视 孩子
Wow, that is some Stone Age shiznit.
哇噢 这可是石器时代的玩意
- Yeah, that's wack. - I need a room with heat.
- 是的 挺古怪 - 我要有暖气的房间
It's summer. It's like 95 degrees in here.
现在是夏天 这里差不多有35度
There he goes again.
他又这么说
I got bunions.
我有拇囊炎
You know, I actually have a poultice I make, using maize and herbs.
其实我有种膏药 我用玉蜀黍棒和草药自制的
Just say corn. Maize is corn, everybody.
说玉米就行了 玉蜀黍棒就是玉米棒
Yeah, he says maize because it sounds more mystical.
是的 他说玉蜀黍 听起来多神秘
Well, I like the way he said it. "Maize."
我喜欢他的说法 "玉蜀黍棒"
- "Maize."
- "玉蜀黍棒"
- It's fantastic, okay? - It's a-maize-ing.
- 听起来很奇妙 不行吗? - 玉蜀黍 真 棒
I just spread it on cloth and I moisten and heat it...
只要抹在布上 湿润加热
...and then I apply it directly to the affected area.
直接将它敷在患处
Okay. Well, my affected area is pretty big.
好吧 我的患处有点大
Oh, no.
噢 不
Mama, I didn't know the Elephant Man lived in your shoe.
妈妈 我还真不知道 原来"象人"住在你鞋子里
How in the world's anybody supposed to get some sleep...
如果知道迈克尔・脚丹在这的话
...knowing they under the same roof as Toe-be Bryant over here?
世上谁还能睡得着?
You're stepping over the line, woman.
你的话过分了 娘娘腔
So, what's with that Labradoodle? It sounds like Stephen Hawking.
那只拉布拉多怎么了? 声音像霍金
Curly, he had his vocal cords clipped.
Curly他声带被剪了
A neighbor filed a complaint...
邻居总是抱怨
...so it was either clip the cords or put Curly down.
所以要么剪掉Curly的声带 要么剪掉它脑袋
Wrong choice.
错误的选择
Come on, he's part of the family, you know?
他是家庭的一份子
Imagine when a burglar comes over and hears that. He must run in terror.
要是小偷听见这个准得吓跑
"Wow, what's that turkey doing in the house?"
"哇噢 那只火鸡在房子里干嘛?"
By the way, Lamonsoff, your son.
对了Lamonsoff 你儿子
What's with the boob thing? Isn't the kid a little old?
怎么还在喝人奶? 都那么大了
He'll be rubbing her boob with his beard soon.
他胡子都快出来了 蹭着会痛吧
He's gonna get a milk mustache on a real mustache. That won't look right.
他会把奶胡子喝到真胡子上 太不妙了
That kid, when he's 10, on his bike...
等那孩子10岁的时候骑着自行车
...the mom's gonna be in the basket, he's gonna be like:
就把他妈放车筐里 像这样
- Come on. - Okay, wait, I got this one.
- 快点 - 好 等等 我来打这个
Chain saw pedicure, 50 points.
锯死足疗师 +50分
Why are they inside right now, anyways?
为什么他们现在还呆在房里?
Why would they not come out here and enjoy the lake...
他们干嘛不出来享受湖景
...or do something in the woods?
或者在树林里玩点什么
There wasn't a time of day that I wasn't outside.
我每时每刻都呆在户外
You know, we weren't. We were always... We were never in.
我们从来不做宅男
All heads on deck!
上甲板锯人头!
Look, there's blood squirting everywhere!
看 血飚得到处都是!
- I can't take it anymore. - Chop his arms off.
- 不能忍了 - 快锯掉他胳膊
Oh, he's being a dad. Look at this.
噢 瞧他要做老爸了
Dad. Don't, Dad. My high score.
别啊老爸 我正高分领先呢
That's it. No more video games. No more cell phones. No more texting.
就这样 禁电玩 禁手机 禁短信
Just from now on, while we're here, stay outside and play.
现在开始 你们就在外面玩
What are we supposed to do?
我们该干嘛?
Just play like normal kids. Come on, move it. Where's Becky?
就像一般孩子那样玩. 快点 开动 Becky在哪儿?
Let's go. Let me show you how the Pilgrims used to hang.
咱们走 带你们去看清教徒被吊死的地方
When we were kids, your dad used to talk us into doing the craziest stuff.
我们还是孩子的时候 你爸总是教唆我们干最疯狂的事
That's right.
没错
Yeah, I remember one time, we got our shower curtains...
是的 我记得有一回咱们把浴帘
...put them in shopping carts and went shopping cart sailing.
装进购物车里 把购物车当船开
Wait, how did you steer?
等等 你们怎么掌舵?
- Well, we didn't. - How'd you stop?
- 没舵 - 那怎么停?
You just smashed into something. That was the fun part.
直接撞上去就行了 那才是乐趣所在
We used to shoot bottle rockets at each other.
我们还互相射塑料瓶火箭
You go for the guy's face because you wanna blind him.
你冲着人家的脸发射 想弄瞎他
Okay, no, that's a little much, pal.
噢 那有点过分了 朋友
No. No, I know. Kids, don't do that.
我知道 孩子们 忘了我刚说的
You know what, erase, reboot.
删除 重启
Okay. Look, look. Make a tree fort. I'll get you started.
看 看 做个树屋 我来教你们
Rob lived in one of those for a year.
Rob在里面住了一年
Why?
为什么?
My dad took away my roller skates.
我爸拿走了我的溜冰鞋
Vietnam flashback.
黑暗的童年
Wait a minute. Are you kidding me?
等一下 开玩笑吗
- What?
- 什么?
Nice.
好极了
Rope on a tree, baby. You know what that means.
树上的绳子 你知道那意味着什么
We get to hang ourselves?
我们要吊死自己?
You see a rope and a lake and that doesn't make you wanna go nuts?
绳子和湖难道没让你 想干点疯狂的事吗?
It makes me... You know what?
它让我想到 我想...
You know what, let me show them.
快让开 我来教他们
- Yeah. - Yeah, baby.
- 好的 - 好的 伙计
Dude, get up on the top rock.
老兄 站到最高那块石头上
- Yeah, you're right. - You gotta back it up, back it up.
- 这就对了 - 再往后点 再往后点
Go, baby.
去吧 伙计
The class is in session.
现场教学
Who wants to see a double flip?
谁想看看双翻转?
Too high.
太高了
- Now drop. - This was a mistake.
- 现在放手 - 这是个失误
I can't let go, I'm too scared.
我不能放手 太害怕了
That was awesome.
真厉害
Oh, God. Oh, God, my leg's snapped.
噢 天哪 我的腿断了
Oh, my God, the bone's sticking out. I need help.
噢 上帝啊 骨头刺出来了 快救救我
It's a stick. I got you.
这是个棍子 你们都上当啦
Very good.
很好
Daddy, that bird is hurt.
爹O 那只鸟受伤了
Oh, my God. I'll go get a shoebox.
噢 天呐 我去找个鞋盒
Here you go.
这边
Hey, did you really land on that bird, man?
嘿 你真的摔那鸟身上了么?
I'm not sure.
我不确定
I did hear a chirp and a crunch-like noise, but that could've been anything.
我好像听到吱吱和折断的声音 但很可能是别的什么
Okay.
好吧
Keith. Sit down. Sit down.
Keith 坐下 坐下
Dad, I wanna sit next to you.
爸爸 我想坐你旁边
Daddy's gonna be down here with his friends first and then...
爸爸要和自己的朋友坐
Lenny, remember we used to come here late night after we got wasted?
Lenny记不记得高中时 我们被放倒以后 半夜来这里
What's "wasted"?
什么是"放倒"?
Nice one, Higgie.
问得好 Higgie
"Wasted." kids...
"放倒"就是...
...is something that happens...
就是你摄入过量...
...when you have a hankering for ice cream.
...冰激凌的状态
- I wanna get wasted.
- 我想被放倒 - 我想被彻底放倒
I wanna get wasted every day.
我希望每天都被放倒
I wanna get chocolate wasted.
我想要被巧克力放倒
No, you don't need to get wasted, it's okay.
不 你不必被放倒
All right, you know what, let me make this easy.
好了 简单点下吧
Seventeen burgers and 17 fries, okay?
17个汉堡和17份炸薯条 好吗?
And that'll be just for me. What are you guys having?
好的 我的够了 你们要什么?
Lamonsoff.
Lamonsoff
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
好好好
That's for everybody. Just put it on that.
这是所有人的 记上
- Oh, you don't have to do that. - I am not gonna have any hamburgers.
- 噢 你不用这样 - 我可不吃汉堡
I'll take some meat loaf, some calzones...
我要一些肉卷 一份卡松尼披萨
...but put the marinara sauce on the side.
酱汁要放旁边
With corn, either on the cob or whatever you got.
还有玉米 带穗的或随便你们
- Are you going to the electric chair? - What?
- 你是要坐电椅了吗? - 什么?
No, he was just kidding, Henry VIII.
他只是在开玩笑 亨利八世
She's eating for two: her and Toe-bo Cop.
她要两份 自己的和迈克尔・脚丹的
But, Mama, they do have bunion rings if you want some.
不过 妈妈 他们有拇囊炎足指环 如果你需要的话
That was good, Lenny.
很好 Lenny
How about some drinks?
要点喝的吗?
I said I'm paying, so take it easy with that, okay?
说了是我请客 别问那么多了好吗?
I'm kidding, everybody. I'm kidding. We can drink all we want.
大伙 我开玩笑的 大家自己点
I'll start it off. I'm gonna have a Coke.
我先开始 我要杯可乐
And I know Donna, she's gonna want a Sprite, correct, sweetie? And...
我知道Donna她要雪碧 对吧甜心
Bean's good with milk, obviously.
显然 Bean喝奶就够了
I want cookies.
我要小饼干
Cookies and MILF.
小饼干和性感妈咪
MILF? Oh, Higgins, thank you so much.
性感妈咪? 噢Higgins 谢谢夸奖
Take it easy, all right? Hey, tuck it away, sweetie.
放松点好吗? 亲爱的 那东西放好
And I'll take a flat water. Voss.
我要Voss矿泉水 (矿泉水中的劳斯莱斯)
What?
什么?
You know, Voss. Or Fiji, if you don't have Voss.
没有的话Fiji水也行 (斐济岛天然自流水直接灌装)
Yeah, you know, anything you got's good.
行了 随便找个白水吧
We have out of the faucet.
我们有饮用水管的水
Like, from a hose?
水管里的?
Tap water.
自来水
What country's that from?
哪个国家的?
Oh, my God. Just get the water. We're done talking about water. Tap water.
噢 天 来杯自来水就行了 别再讨论水了
I go get the Voss from the b...
那我去拿Voss来...
You just sit down, Rita. Just study a menu. The big test is coming.
坐下Rita 好好读菜单 你马上要考试了
I'm sorry, what now?
抱歉 这是干嘛?
He says they have the best burger in town here.
他说这家的汉堡是城里最好的
Really? Since when did you learn to speak Chinese?
是吗? 你什么时候开始学中文了?
It's just something I picked up watching a cooking show.
从中国烹饪节目里学的
That's great. Maybe you should focus a little less on the talking...
很好 也许你应该 少放点注意力在里面的语言上
...and a little more on the cooking.
多放点注意力在做菜方法上
You got told.
对头
You got toe.
对个脚趾头
He comes back.
绝地反击
Mommy, can I have some of her milk?
妈咪 我能尝尝她的奶吗?
There he is.
他在这儿
Joe Hollywood.
好莱坞
Who's that? Dickie Bailey?
这是谁? Dickie Bailey?
Oh, my God.
噢 天呐
Hey, long time no see. How you doing, man?
嘿 好久不见 过得咋样 伙计
You know, that game had some bad calls.
知道吗 那场比赛有些误判
Now, what game are we talking about? The game?
哪场比赛啊?
What, when we were kids 30 years ago, that game?
我们三十年前打的那场吗?
That last shot?
那最后一击?
Your foot was on the line. Shouldn't have counted.
你脚踩线了 不应该算分的
I don't know. I don't remember it quite like that.
我不知道 记得没那么清楚了
You got the rest of the Fugly Five over there, huh?
你们丑五组合都在?
Yes. Yes. They are. The boys are here.
对 是他们 男孩们都在
Boys?
男孩们?
They don't look like they can make it up and down the court anymore.
他们似乎不可能再披挂上阵了
What about you? You put on a few pounds?
你呢? 也长肥了?
From when I was 12?
跟12岁比吗?
Yes, I think so.
确实是
You don't know how to come at me, do you?
你不懂如何刺激我 对吧?
Rematch. I dare you.
再战一场 敢吗?
In basketball? You don't look like you're in the greatest shape either.
打篮球? 你这身材不行哦
I could see having a getting-off-the-couch contest, but...
比赛谁先睡着倒不错 但...
Anytime, anywhere.
任何时候 任何地点
I was just kidding. I really don't wanna do that.
我开玩笑而已 我不想打
Next time you come to town, I'll have plenty of that Boss water for your kid.
下次你来的时候 我会给你的小孩多备些Boss水
- All right. - Wouldn't want him to go thirsty.
- 好吧 - 不能让他渴着了
All right, well, just for the record, it's Voss water, by the way, with a V.
好吧 但实际上是Voss水 胜利那个V字开头的
Okay.
好吧
Gonna be an emotional day tomorrow, spreading the Buzzer's ashes.
明天会很伤感 要撒哨音的骨灰了
Oh, my God.
噢 我的天
The coach requested that we scatter his remains on Mclntyre Island.
教练的遗愿是把他骨灰 分撒在Mclntyre岛上
I got a beautiful ceremony planned.
我准备了一个绝美的纪念仪式
Lenny, you gonna be able to do that? What time do you leave?
Lenny 你也要去吗? 那你什么时候走?
- What are you talking about? - What do you mean, leave?
- 你在说啥? - 什么意思 走?
I forgot to tell you, fellas. We gotta take off in the morning.
忘了说 我们要搭明早的飞机离开
- You're leaving? - You can't leave.
- 你要走? - 你不能走
- We got the ceremony tomorrow. - Lenny's just playing, everybody.
- 明天有纪念仪式 - Lenny开玩笑的 伙计们
No, he's not.
不 他没有
Are you joking?
你在开玩笑吧?
I wanna be there. I mean, we all wanna be there. We gotta go to Milan.
我也想参加 我们都想 但我俩得去米兰
Milan, what? Italy? What's in Milan?
什么 意大利 米兰? 那有什么好的?
It's pretty cool. Roxanne's got her fall line coming out.
超酷 Roxanne的秋季时装秀 在那举办
- Fashion week. - Three nights at the Four Seasons.
- 时装周 - 四季酒店住3晚哦
Eggs Benedict by the pool...
泳池旁有火腿蛋松饼
...PlayStation 3 in every room...
房里有Play Station 3
...and they show boobies on Italian TV.
意大利卫视里还有美胸
I'm going to Italy.
我要去意大利
No, we all... I didn't tell you guys, we're probably gonna go to Italy as a...
不 我们都... 我一直没说 我们大家会去意大利...
Thanks for ruining the surprise.
谢谢你毁掉了惊喜
Lenny, it's not gonna be the same without you.
Lenny 没你在就不完整了
Yeah, come on.
是啊 来吧
Roxanne was cool enough to let us come tonight. This is a big deal.
Roxanne能让我们今晚过来已经很好了 这可是她的大事
Can't Roxanne go without you and you can meet her there?
Roxanne没你不能去吗? 你可以晚点去找她
No, we are a team, me and my lady, and we do everything together.
不行 我们是绝世拍档 形影不离
Last year, we had to skip Becky's school play for Milan.
去年因为米兰 不得不错过Becky的校园话剧
Roxanne.
Roxanne
I thought we were gonna get wasted.
我想我们可以被放倒了
Sweetie. What was I supposed to do, lie to them?
亲爱的 我该怎么办 骗他们吗?
It's not what you said. It's how you said it.
不是因为你的话 而是你的态度
I am not some insensitive work-crazy dragon lady.
我可不是什么神经质的工作狂妇
And I'm not gonna let you depict me as one.
而我也不会让大家这样觉得
We are skipping the dinner in Milan...
所以我们不吃米兰的晚餐了
...spreading the ashes...
改在这里撒骨灰
...and we're leaving first thing Sunday morning.
但周末早上醒了就得走
Lamonsoff, it's 5 in the morning. Can you kill the dog now?
Lamonsoff 现在才凌晨5点 你可以去杀了那狗吗?
Thinking about it.
我再想想
Go ahead. Birdy coming through, everybody.
去吧 小鸟来咯 伙计们
Hey, morning.
嘿 早上好
Morning. Take it right over to the table.
早上好 放那张桌子上吧
How we doing? Something stinks in here.
在干嘛? 臭死了
Gloria and I are making breakfast for everybody.
我和Gloria在给大家做早餐
Using a dehydrator, which never cooks anything above 115 degrees.
用脱水器 食物就不会超过46度
- Those are pancakes? - Ocean pancakes.
- 这些是煎饼? - 海洋煎饼
They're gray. They look like you cut them off an elephant's legs.
灰色的 看上去像是砍的象腿
- I'm not eating that. - It's good for you.
- 我不吃 - 吃了对你有好处
- What is this? - "What is this?"
- 这又是什么? - 什么是"什么"?
A scab?
疮疤?
It's dehydrated banana.
这是脱水香蕉
What happened to a normal banana? Peel a banana and eat it.
你把正常香蕉怎么了? 你可以拨了就吃的
The kids'll love it. It's fun, man. It doesn't go bad.
孩子们会喜欢的 很有意思的 没那么糟
- You slice it thin... - I see what you do.
- 把它切薄... - 我明白了
Maybe you're right. This is good.
或许你是对的 这是好东西
- Is that what it's meant for? - You could.
- 这很有意义? - 可以这么说
Well, I'd rather be hit by dehydrated fruit than processed...
好吧 我宁愿被脱水水果打...
Processed food.
也不要腌制食品
- I'm just kidding around. - You think you can just slap people.
- 我只是开玩笑 - 你觉得可以这么打别人
I don't think that. Don't say that. Come on.
我没这么想 别这么说 拜托
Morning.
早上好
Honey, how is the birdy?
亲爱的 小鸟怎么样了?
Those are the Christian Louboutin shoes.
这是Christian Louboutin的皮鞋啊 (法国奢侈品)
I know I'm overdressed.
我知道我穿得太过正式了
But, sorry, I packed for Milan, not the lake.
抱歉 我这行头是为米兰准备的 而不是为这个山间小湖
Made from acorns.
橡树果做的
So, dude, I'm not eating any of this. You got any normal food? Cereal?
兄弟 我不吃这些 有没有正常点的食物 麦片?
Would you like me to make you egg-white frittata, Mr. Feder?
Feder先生 需要我为您做蛋饼吗?
I mean, is that what you're doing in science class now?
你在试验课上做这个?
Making frittatas?
做蛋饼?
No. We're okay. You can go practice that in your room, though.
不用了 你可以回你房间试验
I know you got the big test coming.
我知道你马上就有个很重要的考试
You know, honey, I think you're overwhelming Lenny.
知道吗 亲爱的 你对Lenny过分了
Here, I got a present for you.
我有个礼物给你
Bacon.
熏猪肉
- Knock yourself out. - Bacon.
- 请便 - 熏猪肉
She gets it.
她买的
She gets it. She gets it. Hey, she gets it.
她买的 她买的 她买的
Thank God she gets it.
感谢上帝她买了
All right, so...
好吧 那么...
Hey, what are you doing?
嘿 你在干嘛
Cooking the bacon.
做熏猪肉
Not in here. That's dead animal flesh. It's not going near the vegan food.
别在这儿弄 那是动物尸体 别靠近素菜
Murderer.
杀人凶手
Fine. What do I do with it? Oh, I know.
好吧 我该怎么处理呢 噢 我知道了
I'm sorry, buddy. I'm sorry.
抱歉 伙计 对不起
Curly. Shame on you.
Curly 你真丢脸
That crazy dog.
疯狂的狗狗
Must have got into some of my leftover pasta fasul.
肯定是吃了我剩下的面
Yeah, Mama, I'm sure that's exactly what happened.
是的 事情就是这样的
It did.
就是它放的
We should get a dog.
我们也养条狗吧
We should get a water buffalo.
我们应该养头水牛
Higgins, what are you doing?
Higgins 你在干嘛?
I don't wear pants at my house, I'm not wearing them in your house. Sorry.
我在家不穿内裤 在你这还没习惯 抱歉
That was a man's ass?
那是男人的屁股?
All right.
好嘞
Yeah.
爽
Let's see this. Look at that.
让我们看看 瞧
That's it, buddy.
就这样 伙计
Okay, throw the rock.
好嘞 扔石头
Skim it.
打水漂
Throw it at a tree.
朝树上扔
Throw it at the lake.
朝小湖扔
Throw it at your brother.
朝你弟弟扔
Hit your head with it.
朝自己的头扔
Just do something.
做点什么吧
Come on.
拜托
What are you doing dressed like that? You hanging out with Jiminy Cricket?
你穿成这样干啥? 要和Jiminy Cricket约会吗?
We were supposed to be going to Milan, remember?
我们本该在米兰的 记得吧?
That's what I packed for.
所以我才这样
Just cut those into shorts.
剪成短裤吧
- We'll play some hoop later. - Pass, dude.
- 我们待会儿滚铁环 - 我不干
You don't want revenge for the time I whupped you?
你不想复仇了?
That was four years ago, homey.
那是四年前的事了 老爸
All I want is to fly to Milan and have some fresh-made gelato.
我只想飞去米兰 吃新鲜的Gelato (意大利经典冰淇淋)
What would your father have done on that one?
如果换成是你父亲 他会怎样?
That one would've been a backhand to the side of the head...
那小子会被反手一大嘴巴
...and possible bleeding from the ear.
力道重至耳朵喷血
My father would've thrown me down the stairs for using the word gelato.
就因为我说Gelato 我老爸会把我撂倒踹下楼
- You got the new Foreman. - Yeah.
- 你的新发明 - 对
Hilliard was trying to make me some tofu Grape-Nuts in there.
Hilliard想给我吃豆腐葡萄仁
Try it out.
吃这个吧
- You cleaned this? - Yeah, I cleaned this thing.
- 你弄干净了? - 对 我搞干净了
- Take it. - Thanks a lot.
- 拿着 - 十分感谢
By the way, Mclntyre Island ain't close.
对了 Mclntyre岛有点远哦
Eat as much as you can, we got a big row ahead of us.
多吃点 待会儿有的受了
You didn't clean that well.
你没完全搞干净
Come on, man. What are you doing to me? Seriously.
拜托 伙计 你对我干了什么?
You don't want your breath to smell like your grandmother's closet?
你可不想口臭媲美马桶吧?
Slow down for Robbie, guys.
慢点 等等Robbie
You're gonna lap me.
你们别干扰我
Beautiful. You gotta respect going to Mclntyre Island.
真美 能去Mclntyre岛是种荣幸
Haven't done that since we're 12.
12岁后就没去过了
Got my first boob there.
我第一次摸胸就在那
- I know. Tracy Thornhill. - Tracy Thorn...
- 我知道 是Tracy Thornhill - Tracy Thorn...
- Yes. - Absolutely.
- 对 - 就是她
A little flat, but I was a fan.
有点飞机场 但我还是很喜欢
All right, Higgins. Is that all you think about is chicks?
好吧 Higgins 你只能想到小妞?
- We got daughters. - That's all you guys think about.
- 我们有女儿了 - 是你们的想法吧
- Difference is, I can do something. - Not true. All right, that's true.
- 区别是 我可以做些事情 - 不对 好吧 是真的
You wanna know what I fantasize about?
知道我意淫的是啥吗?
Candy bars.
棒棒糖
Candy bars?
棒棒糖?
No, I had a bad blood sugar test at my last checkup and Sally cut me off.
我上次体检血糖过高 Sally就禁止我吃了
You're a grown man, how do you deal with that?
你可不是小屁孩 你怎么对付?
Oh, I got my own hidden stash, I'm not stupid.
我有私房菜 我又不蠢
Seriously, I got it all.
真的 什么都有
I got Reese's, Butterfingers, 3 Musketeers.
有Reese Butterfingers 和 3 Musketeers
I hide them under my clothes in the bottom of the hamper.
我把它们藏在衣服里 放在洗衣篮底
It's great because the smell in my sweat socks mask the chocolate smell.
很完美 因为我的湿袜子味 完全压制住了巧克力味
And the looks of your underwear masks the chocolate stains.
而你内裤的尿渍 则完全掩盖了巧克力渍
Hey, hey, hey, hang on, guys. I gotta make a sissy.
嘿嘿嘿 伙计们 我要尿个尿
- No, no, no. - I gotta make a sissy.
- 不不不 - 我得撒个尿
You made three already.
你已经尿了三次了
It must be just oozing out at this point.
肯定是才来的尿吧
Shut up, I'm trying to concentrate.
闭嘴 我要集中精神
It's taking a piss, not the SATs.
只是尿个尿 又不是高考
Are you peeing or is a diesel truck turning off? What the hell is that?
这是尿尿 还是拖拉机熄火? 什么声音?
Listen to hamper bottom.
大家注意听
I think he's sending a message in Morse code.
他是在发莫尔斯电码
Getting old. Stop.
我老了 停
Can't pee. Stop.
尿不出了 停
Reeks like asparagus. Stop.
气味像榴莲了 停
Even though I didn't even have any. Stop.
我就是尿不出了 停
The good news is these girls are gonna say hi to it.
可喜的是有女孩收到信息了
- What's up, ladies? - Hey, girls.
- 怎么了 女士们? - 嘿 女孩们
- That is so gross-looking. - Did you see that?
- 太恶心了 - 看到了吧?
- They don't all look like that, ladies. - You gave that thing 300 pounds...
- 不是所有的都长那样 - 你那家伙有300磅吧
Come on.
拜托
Sick mix tape you made, Robbie.
你做了盘混音磁带吗 Robbie
- Oh, yeah. - Hey, guys, I brought something too.
- 是的 - 嘿 伙计们 我也带了些东西
- Get out of here. - It's the net, yeah.
- 不会吧 - 就是那篮网
Championship game.
冠军赛的
- Let me see that. - I thought the coach should have it.
- 让我看看 - 我觉得教练应该拥有它
Robbie, you gotta put this on the urn, buddy.
Robbie 把这个套骨灰盒上吧
That's cool.
很好
- "Your foot was on the line." - Bailey.
- "你踩线了" - Bailey
What do you think the coach would've said if he heard that trash-talking?
如果教练听到这废话 会怎么说呢?
He'd kick our ass for not kicking his.
如果我们不去把那人灭了 我们就会被教练灭了
- Yeah. - Or we do it the old-school way.
- 对 - 或者用学校的老办法解决
- Have Eric beat his ass for us. - I know, we should.
- 让Eric帮我们灭 - 对 就该这样
No, no, no. I got about eight seconds of fighting, total, left in my life.
不 我这辈子只剩8次灭人的机会了
And I'm saving that in case I get mugged...
我得省着点 以免进了局子被爆...
...or, you know, someone cuts in front of me at Burger King.
或者遇到谁买汉堡时插我队...
- That's my hamper bottom. - We can't delay it anymore, guys.
- 这才是我兄弟 - 不能再耽误了 伙计们
- He just bit his chicken. All right. - Are we going? Okay.
- 他刚咬了一口鸡块 - 现在开始吗?
Let's do it.
开始吧
You know, I think the coach is here with us.
我想教练是与我们同在的
I think he's proud to be here with us in ash form.
他肯定很骄傲 能以骨灰的方式与我们同在
Right here on this island, where we hid from our parents...
此时此刻在这岛上 我们曾经躲避父母的伊甸园里
...and where we're hiding from our wives and children.
现在用来躲避妻儿
Yes, we are.
对 都在这里
Goodbye to you...
再见了...
...friend...
...我们的朋友...
...wise-advice giver...
...我们的领航员...
...buzzer-noise maker.
...哨音复读机...
Rob, come on.
Rob 别这样
I really messed up my marriages.
我确实搞砸了我的婚姻
All of them.
所有的
It was my fault, man.
是我的错 伙计们
I just couldn't hang on.
我就是忍不住
You know, my own daughters...
而我的女儿们
...I don't even hardly know them.
我甚至都不怎么了解她们
- The Buzzer would be ashamed of me. - No.
- 教练肯定以我为耻 - 不会的
Come on, now.
没事的
You got time to patch things up with your daughters.
你还有很多时间去改善和女儿的关系
You just call them when you get back.
回去的时候 给她们电话吧
Actually, they're gonna be here in about 20 minutes.
实际上 还有20分钟 她们就会到这了
Wait, what?
等等 你说什么?
I can use a piece of chicken.
我先啃个鸡腿
No, not with those hands. Coach hands. All right.
别 别用教练的手
Finish the bucket.
整桶都归你了
Actually, I'm still gonna eat it. This is pretty sick, but I'm hungry.
实际上 我还是要吃 虽然很恶心 但我饿死了
Lamonsoff.
Lamonsoff
Go, old bucket. Drop it.
把桶扔了吧
Piece of crap car.
烂车一辆
What?
什么情况?
Hey, Dad.
嘿 老爸
Me?
我?
What?
什么?
- How do you get that... - Hey.
- 这瘪三 - 嘿
...from that?
怎么生出她来的?
Ninety-five percent of that's gotta be from the mother.
百分之九十五遗传自她妈妈
And I am lowballing.
这是最保守估计
Hey, Jasmine.
嗨 Jasmine
How is that possible?
这怎么可能啊?
Oh, no. The Elvis hairs are going up her nose.
噢 猫王的头发插到她鼻子了
She doesn't know what to do.
很尴尬啊
That's sweet.
够体贴
Is this your car?
这是你的车?
My old man lent me this turd.
我的老男人借了我这坨狗屎
Because he doesn't care if I break down in the middle of nowhere...
因为他可不在乎我会半路抛锚
...and get eaten by a bear.
然后被熊吃掉
Your old man?
你的老男人?
Yeah, my boyfriend. Forty-seven years old.
对 我男朋友 57岁
You know, I wish I liked guys my own age...
你知道 我也期盼能喜欢上同龄男生
...but I'm just chasing the dad that ran out on me.
但因为没爹 所以更需要父爱
Hoochie mama.
爽歪歪啊
What does that mean?
啥意思?
I don't know, but it feels right.
不知道 脱口而出的
I hope that car never gets fixed.
我希望那辆车永远修不好
I don't think it will.
我也希望
I took the spark plugs out.
我拔掉了火花塞
Nice.
多谢
We're all looking at the same time. Let's at least take shifts.
我们全部一直盯着不好吧 至少转下头吧
Lamonsoff, you and me look at the tree.
Lamonsoff 你和我先看树那边
McKenzie, we're gonna look at her butt for a little bit.
McKenzie 我们先来看看她的丰臀
All right. Good plan.
好计划
And, shift.
换
What are we doing?
我们在干啥?
Wait, are we all looking at the tree right now?
等等 我们都在看树吗?
Yeah. Let's go back to the ass.
是的 那我们一起看回屁股
Hey, Jasmine. This is Gloria.
嘿 Jasmine 这是Gloria
Gloria, this is Jasmine.
Gloria 这是Jasmine
Hi.
嗨
Oh, look, here comes Grandma Gloria to the rescue.
噢 Gloria奶奶过来圆场了
Let me take a look.
让我看看
Oh, honey.
噢 亲爱的
You've blown your gasket.
密封垫被你动过了
No good.
没啥好看了
That was rough.
大喜大悲啊
If you guys thought seeing them at the car was gross...
如果他俩修车时都算恶心的话
...you should have heard that waterbed action.
那你们应该听听他们的仰泳
Sounded like two grizzlies fighting over a salmon.
就像两只熊在抢鲑鱼
- There was a lot happening. - At least he's getting something.
- 那可是很大的动作啊 - 至少他还能做
I've been shut out since Deanne found out she was pregnant.
老婆怀孕后我就进了冷宫
- That'll happen. - You have sex when they're pregnant?
- 这是肯定的 - 老婆怀孕时还能做?
- Does that hurt the baby? - McKenzie can.
- 不会伤害小孩吗? - McKenzie可以
The baby thinks he's getting a Tootsie Roll.
宝宝会以为是个手指在摸他
- That's good. - Snickers. Snickers.
- 很好 - 像士力架
A little bigger. A little bigger.
还是大点的
I got lucky on Saint Paddy's Day, but she was half-asleep.
那年Saint Paddy节我交了桃花运 不过对方半梦半醒的
And by half-asleep, I mean she was asleep.
说是半梦半醒 其实就是睡着了
Yeah, she was out. Yeah.
对 不省人事了
You're allowed to do that.
其实就是让你上
She'd rather not be awake.
她才不想醒着呢
- Hey, how'd it go with the daughter? - Awkward.
- 嘿 你那女儿怎么样了? - 别提了
I guess the first 20 years of a kid's life is more important than I realized.
或许一个孩子的头20年 要比我想的重要
Yeah. It's always the kids who pay.
是啊 总是孩子在付出
Kids pay.
是孩子
- They pay.
- 是孩子
- They always pay. - But they pay with maize.
- 总是他们付出 - 付出了玉蜀黍
Was good hanging with you guys.
跟你们一起真开心
- No, no, no. We're catching up. - Come on, man.
- 不 不 不 这才开个头呢 - 别扫兴 老兄
I'm glad my family turmoil can provide entertainment for you guys.
我很高兴能把你们的开心 建立在我家的痛苦上
Let's cheer him up. How did we cheer Robbie up in the old days?
给他打打气 我们以前 是怎么给Robbie打气的?
A little arrow roulette?
神箭大轮盘?
- Arrow roulette. - Did we really do that?
- 神箭大轮盘 - 我们真玩过?
Single stupidest thing we ever did.
曾经最白痴的游戏
It was the craziest.
最疯狂的
- Moronic. - Asinine.
- 最弱智的 - 最傻X的
- All right, fellas. - I can't believe we're doing this.
- 好了 各位 - 真不敢相信我们又玩了
How do we always let Lenny talk us into the stupidest stuff?
我们怎么老让Lenny骗来 玩这些白痴玩意?
Remember, whoever stays in the circle the longest wins.
再说下规矩 圈里坚持最久的赢
- I don't like that part. - Whoever stays longest.
- 这可不爽 - 看谁在圈里待最久
Okay, guys, here we go. And a one. And a two...
好了 伙计们 开始了 一 二 ...
Why are we doing this?
干嘛要玩这个?
Go.
放
Hold.
继续飞
- I don't see it. - Where is it?
- 看不见了 - 上哪了?
- I lost it in the sun. - I lose.
- 太阳太大看不清 - 我认输
Curly.
Curly!
I am the champion.
哥赢了!
I beat all you pansies.
哥鄙视你们这些小娘们!
Go, go. Come on, come on, come on. Hurry up.
加油 加油 快抬过去
Oh, you're moving it. You're shaking it.
哦 别动它 别碰它
My hammy.
我腿抽筋了
You complaining about your hammy? I got an arrow in my foot.
别管你的腿了 我脚上还插着箭呢
- Easy, easy. - Stay calm.
- 放松 放松 - 冷静些
What's going on?
怎么了?
- Rob got attacked by an Indian. - Yeah, but he got away.
- Rob被印第安人射到了 - 对 可没抓到
- What? - He got attacked by an Indian?
- 什么? - 他被印第安人射到了?
- Daddy, what happened? - Amber. I'm glad you got here.
- 老爸 你怎么了? - Amber 真高兴你来了
This is my daughter Amber, everybody.
各位 这是我女儿Amber
You got another one?
你还有一个?
- Dude, high five. - No, no high five, my wife's coming.
- 来 伙计 拍一个 - 不 别拍了 我老婆过来了
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God. - God, you made me look at this.
- 额滴神哪 额滴神哪 - 太血腥了
This is killing me.
痛死我了
Bridget, come down here. Daddy's hurt.
Bridget 快过来 老爸受伤了
- You got another one? - Yeah.
- 你还有一个? - 对
Hey.
嘿
- Oh, okay. - "Hey."
- 哦 好吧 - "嘿"
DNA.
虎父无犬女
- Now I get it. - Rob's her mom and dad.
- 明白了 - 这个是Rob跟他自己生的
Now that makes sense.
这个才有道理
Shut up. Foot, arrow, why?
闭嘴 脚啊 箭啊 天啊!
- I think we gotta pull it through. - Oh, let me do it.
- 我觉得要先插到底再拔出来 - 哦 让我来
It was my idea, I said it first.
我想的办法 我先说的
- Don't you hog it. Don't you touch him. - Nobody touch him.
- 你休想独吞 你休想碰他 - 谁都不准碰他
We're gonna be all right here.
大家都不会有事的
All we need is a poultice with some maize that will draw...
只要用玉米棒子熬点膏药 再...
Oh, shut up.
哦 闭嘴
That poultice shit doesn't work.
膏药有鸟用啊?
It never worked. Are you insane?
从来都没用 你脑袋进水了?
Get some alcohol on this bitch.
给老子擦点酒
You should know plenty about that.
这东西你可熟了吧
You were born during the Prohibition.
你可是生在禁酒时期的
And there's the snap.
他发飙了
That was bigger than I thought it was gonna be.
比我想的要厉害
Snap, crackle and pop.
煽下风就爆
Abnormal origin. Pancreas. Abnormal...
异常起源 胰腺 异常...
Such a mess. Such a mess. I can not...
乱透了 乱透了 我没办法...
Excuse me? Princess Rita? Are you gonna help me?
拜托 Rita公主 你是准备一直坐着 还是过来帮个手?
No, Mr. Feder said that I must study for the big final.
不 Feder先生要我复习迎考
What final?
迎什么考?
You tell me. He just keep handing me books.
我还想问你呢 他一直给我书看
Never mind. Did you pack the adapters for Italy?
别管了 去意大利的变压器装好了吗?
Yes, I did in L.A.
在洛杉矶就装好了
Great. Just wipe your hands.
很好 擦下手
I need you to organize all these papers in here very neatly, okay?
帮我把这些文件好好整理下 好吗?
They cannot be ruined.
千万别弄乱了
Hello.
喂?
Hi, this is Roxanne Feder. I just wanna make sure...
嗨 我是Roxanne Feder 我想确认一下...
Mommy. Mommy. It came out. It came out.
妈咪 妈咪 掉了 掉了
Hold on, I'm on the phone, okay?
等等 我还在打电话呢?
My tooth. It fell out.
我的牙掉了
That's great, honey.
很好 亲爱的
Put it under the pillow and I'll put a dollar in there later.
放枕头下面 我会往那塞1块钱的
What?
什么?
Becky, I'm on the phone. I'll put the dollar under...
Becky 我还在打电话呢 我等下会塞1块钱...
Why would you?
怎么是你?
There's no Tooth Fairy?
没有牙牙仙子吗?
I can't believe I just did that.
真不敢相信我居然会这么说
Oh, Lenny, you should have seen her little face.
哦 Lenny 你没看见她那张小脸
I don't know what's wrong with me.
我不知道自己是怎么了
I mean, I try so hard and I can't seem to get anything right.
我是说 我那么辛苦 却老是事与愿违
You made a mistake. Parents make mistakes.
只是犯个错而已 为人父母难免犯错
Remember the time I told Greg that babies come from mommies' poop...
还记不记得我告诉Greg 小宝宝是从妈咪的屁屁里拉出来的
...and he kept looking in the toilet for a baby brother?
然后他就一直在马桶里找小弟弟
- That's not funny. - I'm just saying.
- 这可不好笑 - 我只是说说
Can you hear me now? Okay.
能听到吗? 很好
I just feel...
我只是觉得...
What about now? Now can you hear me?
现在呢? 能听到吗?
I feel like I ruined her childhood.
我觉得自己毁了她的童年
She was gonna find out eventually.
总有一天她会知道的
Eventually, but not today.
总有一天 但不是今天
Can you hear me now? This is so cool.
能听到吗? 这太酷了
- Are you there? - Hey, didn't I say no cell phones?
- 你还在吗? - 嘿 不是说不准打手机吗?
I thought we had a deal.
我想我们说好了的
- What? - What's up, Dad?
- 什么? - 怎么了 老爸?
Are those cup phones?
是纸杯电话?
Yeah, Charlotte taught us. Cool, huh?
是啊 Charlotte教我们的 酷吧?
Hey, check out Becky's.
嘿 来看看Becky的
Look, Dad. I have cup waiting.
爸爸 还有电话等我呢
I gotta call you back, I'm on with SpongeBob.
等下再打给你 我在跟海绵宝宝说话呢
Was that a turkey?
那是火鸡吗?
Yo, Andre, can you hear me?
哟 Andre 听得到吗?
Crystal clear. Can you hear me?
非常清楚 你呢?
Oh, yeah.
哦 听得到
So the best thing about these is we can leave a cup in the shower...
最帅的就是把杯子放Jasmine浴室里
...and listen to Jasmine clean herself tomorrow.
这样明天就能听见她冲澡了
- What? - Oh, my God!
- 什么? - 哦 老天爷!
May I borrow this?
能借来用下吗?
Attention, children.
注意了 孩子们
There's been a request from the phone company.
这里是电话公司
Would you please install cup phones in every adult bedroom right away?
你们能不能马上给大人的房间 都安上纸杯电话?
Thank you. All right. Go. Move it, move it, move it.
谢谢 好了 去吧 行动 行动 行动
I said, move it. Move it.
我说了 行动 行动
Yes, I have always been the Tooth Fairy.
对 牙牙仙子一直都是我扮的
No, Bean's mommy is the Tooth Fairy for his family.
不 Bean妈妈是他们家的牙牙仙子
I just cover our family.
我只管我们家
No, do not tell Bean, okay?
不 别告诉Bean好吗?
Becky, I love you so, so, so much, okay?
Becky 我好爱好爱你的
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
我很抱歉 亲爱的
- Okay, you're costing me a fortune. - No, you hang up first.
- 好了 我都快倾家荡产了 - 不 你先挂
Let's go. This is gonna be a high cup bill.
快挂了 电话单子要超支了
It's nice to put maize on your arrow wound.
我真喜欢在你箭伤上敷药
What the hell is that? Is that Gloria laughing?
那是什么鸟状况? Gloria在笑?
She's still here after he had a snap on her like that?
他刚发完飙他们就和好了?
- She forgave him right away. - You are my special lady.
- 她马上就原谅他了 - 你是我的美人
And you are my one-footed maize-covered lover.
你是我的独脚玉米"棒"男人
Okay, come on, we gotta go to sleep.
好了 睡觉吧
We're going to Milan tomorrow, right? A long flight.
明天还要去米兰是吧? 要飞好久呢
Let's get our rest.
休息吧
Somebody kill that turkey.
谁去把那火鸡宰了
Is that getting me horny?
我这是性奋吗?
Yes.
没错
You promise you'll still feed her after we leave?
答应我等我们走了你还喂她
I promise.
我答应你
Mommy, that's my milk.
妈咪 那是我的奶
Bean, we have to learn how to share, even with birds.
Bean 我们要学会分享 哪怕是只鸟鸟
But he's going to drink you dry.
可他都把你喝干了
This is good.
扔得好
I got it three times.
我的蹦了3次
Donna, you wanna try?
Donna 你要来试试吗?
Sure. But I stink at sports.
当然 可我不擅长运动
That's all right. Here.
没事的 给
- Hold it like this. - Like this?
- 这样拿 - 这样?
Get down low and throw it, and let the rock do the magic.
手放平再扔出去 然后这石子就有翅膀了
- Nice. - Oh, I skipped it.
- 很好! - 噢 蹦起来了
- Good job, Donna. - Bravo.
- 扔得好 Donna - 太帅了
Do you know how to skip rocks?
你会打水漂吗 Feder太太?
Are you kidding me? I am the best at this.
你问我? 姐可是高手啊
Give me that. Now, watch, now.
拿来 都看好了
Oh, my God, baby, are you okay?
哦 天啊 宝贝 你没事吧?
Yeah, Mom, I'm just glad to see you having some fun.
没事 妈妈 没想到你也那么喜欢玩
I'll take your luggage to the car, Mr. Feder.
我这就把你行李放车上去 Feder先生
That's not my luggage, that's textbooks.
那不是我的行李 那是你的课本
That's nice of you to take your own stuff down.
我很高兴你能自己搬行李
You're okay. Come on.
你没事的 加油
Come on, man. Already? You're leaving?
得了 伙计 你们这就要走了?
Yes, I gotta go.
对 非走不可了
Do you need any help getting to the airport?
要送你们去机场吗?
We got a little problem.
亲爱的 有点小问题
What? What happened?
怎么了? 出什么事了?
I forgot how to skip a rock.
我不会打水漂了
Now, I think it's gonna take a couple of days to figure it out.
我觉得我需要几天复习一下
So...
所以...
...I think we better stay.
我们先别走了吧
Are you kidding me?
你没开玩笑吧?
For reals, Mom? We're not leaving?
真的吗 妈妈? 我们不走了?
I don't need to see a bunch of starving models walking around in my clothes.
不走了 没必要去看那些瘦骨嶙峋的 模特穿着我设计的衣服瞎逛
Yeah, why would you wanna see models when you can see this?
是啊 看什么模特啊? 他们哪会哥这样
See? You couldn't get that in Milan.
瞧见没? 在米兰可看不到
You.
你啊你
What do you wanna do today? Anything.
你今天想干什么? 随便吩咐
I don't know. You tell me.
不知道 你说咧?
What was your favorite thing to do when you were 12 and it was sunny?
你12岁时遇到好天气会最想玩什么?
Well, I can't do that.
哦 这可不行
Maybe go to a water park.
要不... 去水上世界吧
What are we waiting for?
那还等什么?
- Seriously? - Let's load up the car, people.
- 真的假的? - 准备好车子出发
Are you kidding me?
真的假的啊?
- I'm not taking my shirt off. - I'm not taking my shirt off either.
- 我不脱衣服 - 我也不脱衣服
You're wasting it.
都浪费了
Sorry.
抱歉
It's all right.
没事
It's actually not that bad.
其实味道还不差
- Ladies' day. - All right? You're in charge.
- 今天可是美女秀 - 好吗? 你看好他们
I have to go number two.
我要嘘嘘
Okay, hang on, son.
好吧 再憋会 儿子
Hey, Dad.
嘿 老爸
Hey. Where you guys been?
嘿 你们去哪了?
Well, we didn't bring our swimsuits, so Marcus went to take us to buy some.
我们没带泳衣 Marcus带我们去买了
We got them at a store called Naughty and Nice.
是家叫"小坏坏"的店
Marcus said it was the only one open.
Marcus说就这一家开着
The only place open? For bathing suits? In the summer?
大夏天就这么一家卖泳衣?
We got my bathing suit at Stop and Shop.
我这件是在"走过路过不错过"买的
Now, that's... I like that one.
这件...我喜欢
Let's hit the water slide.
去玩旋风滑道喽!
Water slide.
旋风滑道!
What a beautiful day.
真是个好日子
- God. It's a girls' day. - I know.
- 今天可是美女秀啊 - 说的是啊
It is hot.
好热啊
Oh, boy.
哦 伙计
- Are we really doing bathing suits? - God, it's hot.
- 真要穿泳衣吗? - 哦 这天真热
Come on, girls. We don't know these people. Who cares?
得了 姐们 反正又没人认识我们 怕什么?
You're right, who cares? I've been working all summer on this six-pack.
对啊 怕什么? 整个夏天 我都裹着这破布
All right.
好了
How do you feel about that?
感觉如何啊?
- Baby got front. - Go, D. Go, D.
- BB到前面来 - 来吧 大D 来吧 大D
Come on, Sally, it's your turn. Take it off.
该你了 Sally 衣服脱掉
Oh, no. I have a bit of a chill, actually.
哦 不 我觉得有点冷
Gloria, how about you?
Gloria 那你呢?
I don't own a bathing suit. But I like to go nude.
我没泳衣 但我喜欢全光
- No, no, no. - There's children here.
- 不 不 不 - 这里还有小孩呢
Hey, somebody likes what he sees.
嘿 有人在打望呢
- Daddy, this line's not even moving. - I know.
- 老爸 这队伍稳如泰山啊 - 就是
- I want Mommy's milk.
- 说的是 - 我要喝妈咪的奶
I know you do, son, but...
我知道你要喝 儿子 可是...
He wants mommy's milk. Give him some mommy's milk.
他要喝妈咪的奶 就给他妈咪的奶啊
Mommy's milk! Mommy's milk!
妈咪的奶! 妈咪的奶!
No. No. Damn it.
不 不 该死
No more Mommy's milk, okay?
不准再喝妈了
You want milk, you're drinking regular milk.
要喝 就喝牛
- Here, kid. - Hey.
- 拿来 小朋友 - 嘿
Don't give me any guff right now. Here's a buck. Run along. Run along.
别跟老子废话 给你1块钱 快滚
Here. Drink the milk out of the carton.
拿着 把盒子里的牛奶喝了
I don't know if Mommy will want me to.
不知道妈咪让不让我喝
All right, just drink it, okay? Just like Daddy does. Let me show you, okay?
你就只管喝好了 看你老爸怎么喝的 老爸教你喝好不好
Okay.
好
I'm just like Daddy.
我跟老爸一样了
There you go.
很好
No more booby milk.
不吸人奶了
More for us.
留给我们吸
So, ladies, how do we get Mr. Banana Hammock...
各位姐们 有什么办法让肌肉男先生
...to come over here, where we can get a better look at him?
到我们这来? 我们要好好看看他
Okay. Well, there's two big advantages to breast-feeding...
好吧 这就是母乳喂养的优势之一
...and I'm gonna put mine to work.
现在我就来发挥一下
Sally.
Sally
That's it, girl.
对了 姐们
Oh, my goodness.
哦 天啊
- Work that umbrella pole, baby. - Sally. Oh, my God.
- 来个伞管舞 - Sally 额滴神哪
- Oh, it's definitely working. Yeah. - You're good at that.
- 哦 鱼要上钩了 - 你真行啊
- Oh, my God, he likes it. - Look at him flex.
- 哦 鱼快上钩了 - 你看他那身材
No, continue.
不 别停啊
All right, doing the back-door shuffle. Cutting the line. Go.
好吧 走后门进 我们不排队了 走
Don't get hurt.
当心
Go, go, go.
走 走 走
Dad, are we allowed to go through here?
爸爸 我们可以走这里吗?
Absolutely not, but we're doing it anyway.
当然不能 但我们还是照样进
All right, your cool dad found this back in the day.
想当年这可是你们无敌老爸找到的
Go up the ladder.
顺着梯子上去
It's dark in there. Maybe you should hold my hand.
这里面好黑的 牵好哟
I'm scared.
我好怕的
Hey. Come here, come here.
嘿 过来 过来
Don't fall for that crap. You stay away from him.
别给那人渣搭上了 离他远点
What are you talking about? He's gay, isn't he?
你说什么呢? 他不是玻璃吗?
No. He just seems gay.
不 他只是像玻璃
He's a genius.
他可是老油条了
Go, go, go.
走 走 走
Alrighty, who's next?
好了 下一个是谁?
Now's a good time. Charlotte.
是时候了 Charlotte
You're up first.
你先上
- There you go. - Have fun, Charlotte.
- 去吧 - 玩得开心 Charlotte
There you go. Who's next? Go.
走了 下一个 来
- Is he coming this way? - He's coming towards us right now.
- 他朝这边来了吗? - 他朝我们过来了
- This is good now. - He is.
- 现在一切正常 - 没错
Whatever you do, don't fart.
不管怎么着 别放屁
Hey, what's up, ladies?
嘿 你们好啊 美女 呵!
So you're from around these parts, eh?
都是本地人吗? 呵!
Yeah, I'm from Saskatchetoon. That's up in Canada, eh?
俺是从Saskatchetoon 那旮哒来的 加拿大人 呵!
You American ladies, you've been out to Saskatchetoon, eh?
美国的美女们 去过Saskatchetoon么? 呵!
Hoseteasers.
死相!
Everything was on steroids except for his voice.
一晃眼纯爷们 一张嘴嫩娘们
Go, go, go.
走 走 走
Out, out, out.
上 上 上
Now, now, now.
快 快 快
Next.
下一个
All right, who's next? Hey, weren't you guys just here?
好了 下一个是谁? 嘿 你们不是刚刚玩过了吗?
No. I think you have us confused with some other people.
没有啊 我想你认错人了
I don't think so, you're two of the hottest chicks I've ever seen in my life.
不可能 你们俩可是 我这辈子见过的最正的妞
- Hey. - What?
- 嘿 - 干嘛?
- These are my daughters. - Right.
- 她们可是我女儿 - 是啊
Her, definitely.
她 肯定是
Because she's fugly, just like you.
跟你一样 奇挫无比
- Hey. - Now, who's next?
- 嘿 - 下一个
Dad. Come on. Hurry up, I wanna go to Pirate's Plunge.
爸爸 快点 我要玩海盗速滑
One second. Yeah, we're going on all the rides. We're doing them all.
等一下 亲爱的 我们都会玩的
We'll have fun.
我们会很开心的
Are you making a sissy?
你在尿尿吗？
No, I'm not.
不 我没有
You know they put a chemical in the pool that turns urine blue.
要知道泳池里有化学试剂 遇到尿会变成蓝色
No, no, no, that's an old wives' tale, sweetie. That's an old wives' tale.
不 不 不 那是无稽之谈 宝贝 不要相信
Oh, my God. You're humiliating me.
上帝 你真让我丢脸
Mama, Mama.
妈妈 妈妈
Wanna take a picture?
想照相吗？
All right. A little farther.
好的 站远一点
Farther.
远一点
Gotcha.
成功了
I don't know about this one, Dad. It's kind of steep.
这个我不太会玩 爸爸 有点陡
It's a little steeper than I remember.
比我记忆中的是要陡一些
Okay, let's go on another ride.
我们还是去玩别的吧
- I don't like it either, yeah. - Come on, we'll get out of here.
- 我也不喜欢 - 走吧 去别处玩
Good thing the kid chickened out so you don't have to go, right, Feder?
小孩子怕了 所以你就有借口了 对吧 Feder?
Why don't you hire somebody to do it for you, Mr. Richie Rich?
干脆花钱请个人帮你吧 有钱人？
Good idea. Hey, Wiley, what's up, man?
- 好主意 - Wiley 好吗 伙计？
- Step aside. Let me get this on. - All right, son.
- 站开点 让我来 - 好样的 儿子
Hasta la vista, chicken shiznit.
拜拜 胆小鬼
Yeah, look at him go.
看看他
Go, kid.
上啊 孩子
That was good. That was very nice.
真好 真漂亮
All right, now I want some of this.
我也想玩玩
Look at this. Look at this.
瞧见没
- What happened there? - Attaboy. Way to go, Greggie.
- 瞧见没 - 好小子 上啊
Backwards, huh? Look at him.
倒着来? 瞧瞧
Backwards, baby.
倒着 宝贝
You're up, Hollywood.
到你了 好莱坞
I'm up? All right. I don't know how you follow backwards.
我来? 好吧 我不太会倒着跳
Just pay attention to the dismount, would you?
但我有自己的起跳哟
Looks like second place again, Bailey, huh?
看样子又是第二名了 Beiley
- Hear this guy? Second place. - Second place.
- 听到没？ 第二名 - 第二名
Go down there hanging by your feet.
用脚倒挂着跳
Show these idiots.
让这些白痴看看
By my feet?
用我的脚？
Yeah.
当然了
Is that safe?
安全吗？
What do you care? You're an animal. You're an animal.
担心什么 你是只野兽 你是只野兽
I'm an animal.
我是只野兽
Wiley.
Wiley
- Why don't you do it? - I got kids.
- 你怎么不来？ - 我有孩子
Yeah, Wiley.
Wiley
Wiley, Wiley, Wiley.
Wiley Wiley Wiley
Oh, you don't need to do this.
你没必要这样做
I'm an animal.
我是只野兽
I can't get my foot out.
脚 卡 住 鸟
That's how you do it, boy.
就像这样 孩子
- Becky. - You can do this.
- Becky - 你可以的
- Good. There you go. - Give me a five.
- 好的 就这样 - 来击个掌
Roxanne, look at him. It's like he totally forgot about me.
Roxanne 你看他 好像完全把我忘了
Typical man.
典型的男人
They take all you can give and then they trade you in for some cow.
拿走你能给的一切 然后 为了买牛什么的就把你给卖了
I don't know what I'm supposed to do with these now.
我不知道怎么处理我的奶了
I do.
我知道
Now, see that, buddy?
看到没 伙计
I did the old bank shot. Bank's open. Pick a spot. Aim for it.
这是老式擦板球 选个地方 瞄准
Oh, yeah. Your dad'll go 50 for 50 with these.
你爸爸就是这样百发百中的
Really? Because on the Wii, the bank shot never works.
真的吗? 因为Wii里 擦板球绝对不行
Yeah? Well, you should Wii-turn it and get a Wii-fund.
是吗? 那你应该去找他们退钱
Tim Duncan's had about a hundred game winners with that bad boy.
Tim Duncan已经是100胜投手了
Honey, are you watching me?
宝贝 看我
Oh, baby, that was hot.
天啊 帅呆了
- Come here, let me show you. - Way to go, baby.
- 过来 我教你 - 过去吧
Move it, move it, move it. What you gotta do is...
跑 跑 跑 你要做的是
See the box up there? Top right corner of it?
看到上面那个篮筐了吗? 右上角?
Hello?
喂
Focus, boy, focus. Get off of that.
集中精力 孩子 别看那些了
Lamonsoff, focus.
Lamonsoff 看我这儿
Oh, my God, what a perv.
天啊 坏蛋
He's totally checking me out.
色咪咪的一直盯着我
He wasn't... I don't know.
他不是在... 我不知道
All right, come on. Go ahead.
来吧 投篮
Follow through. Keep the hand up.
坚持住 保持手向上
Are you kidding me?
不会吧?
Respect.
太崇拜你了
See how good you can be when you wear normal clothes?
换上了普通衣服 依然这么棒
- Hey, Mama. - Hey, baby.
- 妈妈 - 宝贝
How come you're not out there playing basketball?
你怎么不去打篮球?
- You know I got... - You got bunions. Where's Kurt?
- 你知道我有... - 你有脚趾囊肿 Kurt在哪儿?
Come on, are you scared?
来吧 你害怕了?
What's wrong with you?
怎么了?
Stop it.
够啦
Somebody's in trouble.
有人要倒霉了
Not looking good.
不妙啊
I do the same thing.
我做了同样的事
All right, I did everybody's first shot for them.
好了 每个人的头杯酒我给喝了
Now you do the second one.
轮到你们喝第二杯了
Come on, now.
现在开始
No, nobody's doing shots.
没人那么喝
We got kids here, dummy. Gotta wake up in the morning.
孩子都在呢 蠢驴 明天还要早起
We're gonna biz beers instead. Who's got beers? Check them off.
那我们就拼啤酒 谁要啤酒? 举手
- I'm gonna go with one. - Yeah, I'll stick with coffee.
- 我就喝这一瓶 - 我只喝咖啡
- I'm having this many. - Cheers.
- 我这儿有很多这个 - 干杯
- I'm breast-feeding, I don't drink. - I'm just having Metamucil tonight.
- 我在哺乳 不能喝酒 - 我今晚只喝泻药
What's wrong with you guys?
你们都怎么了
We used to come up here and party, man, and get wasted.
我们以前在这儿都会玩倒下的
You losers.
你们真没用
Don't worry, you'll grow up one day. You just have to meet the right girl.
别担心 你会长大的 你需要一个对的女孩
Oh, my older sister would be perfect for you.
我姐姐跟你会是绝配
What?
什么?
She's legally blind, but she can see shapes.
医生说她瞎了 但她还能看见轮廓
Anyways, Roxanne, how did you and Lenny meet?
Roxanne 你是怎么和Lenny认识的？
That's a good question.
问的好
How did this blob of crap, no offense...
这坨废物是怎么 我没恶意...
...meet this lovely seorita?
...遇到这位墨西哥辣妹的
Oh, he came into the department store where I was working.
他在我的百货公司逛
I helped him.
我帮了他
He wanted me to try this skirt on.
他让我试穿一条短裙
Oh, the old "try on the skirt" trick.
让人试衣服的老把戏
I got you. Very sneaky, sis.
我知道了 真狡猾
Yeah, he did trick me. Afterwards he made me try on a bra and...
确实是这样的 后来他又让我试胸罩
Hey, I was just trying to help.
结果就 "我只是帮帮忙"
- Exactly. - Okay, okay. I did like him a little.
- 确实 - 好吧 我是有点喜欢他
It was a good day.
那天天气很好
Oh, God! Oh, my water. My water's breaking.
天啊 我的羊水 我的羊水破了
The baby's coming!
孩子要出来了
- Are you serious? - Oh, yeah.
- 真的吗? - 天啊
Oh, you.
你真是的
Oh, my God.
天啊
I got you, I got you, I got you.
我骗到了你 你 还有你
All right.
你强
I'm just playing.
我喜欢玩的
Oh, my God, it's...
我的天 这是
Do you know this song? Oh, this song's the best.
你们知道这首歌吗? 最动听的
This song is the best.
这首歌我最爱了
Oh, this song gets me so horny.
这首歌让我好性奋
You know, I was thinking that, but now not so much.
我也是 但现在又平静了
I'd like to claim credit for that.
我相信性奋这事
Because that's all part of my "get some nookie" playlist.
因为我就是靠这歌上垒的
Get the ladies on the dance floor, and I got my lady right here.
带上女士下舞池 现在就是她
Come on, honey.
来吧 亲爱的
- That was a really good move. - Let's do this.
- 是个好办法 - 我们来跳舞
Yeah, you guys dance.
跳舞
- It has been a while. - A long while.
- 好久了 - 好长一段时间
I know how much you love to dance.
我知道你有多喜欢跳舞
Oh, you know me, I'm a regular Shabba-Doo.
我是Shabba Doo的铁杆粉丝
Look at you.
看看你
All sexy. Deanne.
多性感的Deanne啊
You should change your name to Deyonc.
你应该改名叫D昂斯 (碧昂斯...)
Yeah, so now he thinks I'm sexy, huh?
现在有人觉得我性感了？
Can I just enjoy a dance with my fine-ass wife?
能让我和我的性感老婆 好好跳一曲吗？
Yes. To the whitest song ever. Yes.
好吧 冲着史上最纯情的歌 好的
Yes, this is the whitest song I've ever heard.
史上最纯情的歌
You know, Lenny, you were right about bringing us here.
Lenny 带我们来这儿非常明智啊
This place is really special.
这个地方太特别了
It is, right?
对吧?
Nothing's going on here, and I love it.
在这儿自由自在 我很喜欢
Roxanne, I have made out with about 25 different girls in this very spot...
Roxanne 我在这地儿摆平了25个女孩
...and I want you to be number 26.
我要你做第26个
As long as I'm the last one.
只要我是最后一个
Oh, that's a guarantee.
这我绝对保证
I'm horny too.
我也很性奋
Hey, what are you doing? You idiot.
你在干嘛? 你这个白痴
Lamonsoff. What are you doing up?
Lamonsoff 你也来啦?
- I gotta tell you, it was crazy. - What?
- 跟你说吧 太疯狂了 - 什么?
Sally. She just attacked me.
Sally 她刚才太主动了
Like never before. It was insane.
从没有这样过 真是疯了
I just did the same thing with my woman.
我老婆刚刚也这样
Really?
真的?
Hey, where's Saskatchetoon?
Saskatchetoon在哪儿?
Yeah. I don't know.
我不知道
- What am I? - A hoseteaser.
- 我是什么? - 一匹母马
- And where are you from? - Saskatchetoon.
- 你从那里来? - Saskatchetoon
Look at this.
看看这个
- And what am I? - A hoseteaser.
- 我是什么? - 一匹母马
- And where are you from? - Saskatchetoon.
- 你从那里来? - Saskatchetoon
What are we gonna do with Higgins?
我们怎么处理Higgins?
Yeah, and you know what? This is what pisses me off:
你知道吗 他真让我来气
You can't be passed-out drunk, single, with no responsibility and not pay.
他不能单身烂醉在这 不用负任何责
You have to be hurt for that.
他应该为此受点损失
Yeah.
没错
Sweetheart?
亲爱的?
You fell asleep on the couch again.
你又在沙发上睡着了
You know you supposed to go to your room.
你应该回房睡
You're bad.
你真坏
No.
不
Marcus, the bird is all better.
Marcus 这只鸟没事了
Marcus. He wants to talk to you.
Marcus 他想和你谈谈
Marcus, you're gonna be the best lifeguard at the whole pool.
Marcus 你是游泳池里最棒的救生员
Hold your breath, honey.
屏住呼吸
Who's that?
谁啊?
Oh, it's mommy's boyfriend.
妈妈的男朋友
The one who touches you.
就是他碰你的
He's crying, he's crying.
他哭了 他哭了
- All right, quiet. - Hi, Mama.
- 好了 安静 - 妈妈
- All right. It's all right. - Mama?
- 没事了 没事了 - 妈妈？
- Okay, baby. It's okay, precious.
- 好了 宝贝 没事的
I'm gonna take you upstairs.
我带你上楼
Go and put your PJ's on, okay? You can't fall asleep...
给你换上睡衣 你不能睡在...
You can't just sleep anywhere, you know that.
你不能睡在这儿的
You go to your room.
回你房间去
- Go to sleep. - You go to your room.
- 去睡觉 - 回你房间
- What you doing? - Come here.
- 你在干嘛？ - 过来
This isn't a closet. This is your bedroom.
这不是壁橱 这是你的房间
Okay? It's also your bathroom. You can make a pee-pee.
这也是你的浴室 你可以尿尿
I'm making a pee-pee.
我在尿尿
Happy Fourth of July, everyone.
独立日快乐
It's the birdy's Independence Day too, so keep your fingers crossed, honey.
小鸟也要独立的 所以为其祈祷吧
- She did it, Daddy. - Here we go.
- 她飞了 - 是的
- Bye, birdy. - She's flying.
- 再见 小鸟 - 她飞走了
She's gonna be a veterinarian. Is this girl incredible or what?
她想做兽医了 难以置信
That's so sexy. What did you say?
真性感 你在说什么？
Oh, I think that she said:
我想她在说
Milan.
米兰
You know, these guys at the store were talking so much smack...
知道吗 那些商店里的家伙刚刚吵着
...about this basketball rematch that's supposed to go on.
那场篮球赛应该重新打一次
Well, I'm glad we're getting these uniforms ready.
真高兴我们已经准备好球衣了
No more drinkie.
不能再喝多了
Did you really sleep in the closet, you drunk?
你真的睡在壁橱里了 真醉了?
Think so.
是的吧
No.
不
Oh, God, Higgins.
天啊 Higgins
- That's disgusting. - You slob.
- 真恶心 - 你个笨蛋
Oh, I had the sexiest dream about a little blond girl, though.
我做了个大春梦 虽然只是个金发小美女
I think it was a dream.
那应该只是个梦
- Oh, nice. Classy. - Sick.
- 天啊 - 恶心
These deviled eggs would really be good if you had some marinara sauce.
如果放些意大利酱 这些鸡蛋沙拉会特别美味
Oh, it's Lenny's phone.
Lenny 的电话
Hello?
喂？
All right, here we go.
好的
Oh, that's a three.
又是个3
That's one, two, three, ladder. Ladder.
一 二 三 梯子 梯子
Oh, that's it. The rich keep getting richer.
就是这样 有钱人总会更有钱
All right. All right. Schniggly is here.
好吧 好吧 Schniggly来了
So, come on, Robbie, tell the man what's going on.
好了 Robbie 告诉他发生了什么事
He doesn't care.
他才不感兴趣
- Tell him. - What are you talking about? Tell him.
- 告诉他
Gloria and I are thinking about having a baby.
我和Gloria打算要个孩子
How great is that?
多好啊
That's great.
太好了
You know, the good news is she can't get any more stretch marks.
好消息是她不会有更多的妊娠纹了
- Boy, that's a good one. - Come on.
- 那是好事 - 好吧
You know, the good thing also is Gloria and the kid can share diapers.
还有个好消息 就是Gloria和孩子可以分享尿布
Man. You see, that's just ugly.
这话真难听
He doesn't get it. He's not in a committed relationship.
他不懂 他又没结婚
He can't, because he can't stay
他不会明白的 因为他安定不下来
Oh, look. He's just mad because all the girls I go out with...
瞧 他生气了 因为跟我约会的女孩
...are 70 to 80 years younger than his wife.
都比他老婆年轻70到80岁
Can't stop.
还停不下来了
The last one I was with, she's blond, she's tall, super hot. Not your type.
我的上一个 金发 高挑 性感 不是你喜欢的那种
Me and blondie, we start going at it and we're shaking the bed...
我和金发美眉正起劲 一起晃床
Shaking the bed? What does shaking the bed mean?
晃床? 什么意思?
I don't know, I just know wetting the bed. I don't know...
我不懂 我只懂湿床
And then, right at the "good part." you know?
然后就进正题了
This picture behind, right on the wall, falls and goes:
结果墙上挂的画掉了下来
Hits her on the forehead.
砸到她的额头上
She cut her head.
伤到头了
It cuts her. I didn't slow down.
破了条口 但我没有停
I just throw her two aspirins, she yaps on them like a Frisbee dog.
我扔给她两片阿司匹林 她像接飞盘的狗一样叼住
I am tired. Marcus, your snoring kept me up all night long.
好累啊 Marcus 你的鼾声让我一夜未眠
You're a dead man. Get back here.
你死定了 回来
Come back here. That's my baby girl. I thought you were my friend.
回来 那可是我女儿 亏我当你是朋友
Leave me alone. Drink your maize.
走开 回去喝你的玉蜀黍
You're gonna pay this time.
你这次死定了
You bastard. I'll show you how to be nice.
混蛋 让你好看
- Bad turtles. - You evil pig.
- 臭乌龟 - 你个恶棍
- Robbie, wait. - He's psycho.
- Robbie 等等 - 你个疯子
Stop. Stop.
停 停
Hey, break it up, man. Jeez, guys.
滚开
- All right. - Calm down.
- 好的 - 冷静
Buddy. Buddy. What's the problem?
哥们 怎么了
Oh, yeah. Arrow foot.
这下好了 箭脚
- Come here, baby. - Come on. Why are you fighting?
- 搞什么 - 你们干嘛打架？
Good to see midget wrestling again.
很高兴又看到侏儒摔跤了
How could you do that? That's my daughter.
你怎么可以这样? 她可是我女儿
- Do what? - Shake the bed with her.
- 怎样了? - 和她一起晃床
You think I would do that to you?
你觉得我会这样吗?
Out of any of us you'd be the one to do that.
你是我们当中唯一一个会这么做的
You did sleep with Stimpson's mother.
你连Stimpson的妈妈都睡过
I didn't even know that guy. He was your friend. I barely knew him.
我根本不认识他 他是你朋友 但我不认识啊
She grabbed my wiener, I told you guys.
而且是她逼我的 我说过的
- That's his daughter. It's different. - Me and him?
- 那可是他女儿 不一样 - 我和他?
Okay. Maybe I flirted with him, but that was just to get your attention.
好吧 也许我和他调情了 但我只是想引起你的注意
- Well, what about his snoring? - I heard it too.
- 那打鼾是怎么回事? - 我也听到了
Oh, no. Twice?
不 又来了
We heard it from three rooms away.
隔着三个房间都能听到
He's off the hook. You know Marcus wouldn't be with your daughter.
那就不可能了 Marcus不可能找你女儿的
I mean, not that she's... You know what I'm saying.
我的意思是 不是说她... 你懂的
- Well, what happened to your head? - When I was changing into my PJs...
- 你头怎么了 - 我换睡衣时
...I got the feeling that some perv was looking through my window...
感觉有变态在窗外偷看
...so I went to go close the shade and I tripped and hit my head.
我过去关窗户时 不小心失足撞了头
Yeah, dude, that's your daughter.
兄弟 那可是你女儿
I'd never be with her. You're my best friend, man.
我压根没和她在一起 你可是我的好哥们
And Jasmine'd never be with me, because I'm me.
Jasmine也不会和我在一起的 因为是我
Look, sorry I don't have my whole life together, like Lenny.
看 我没有像Lenny那样 跟着谁一辈子
Oh, together, like Lenny.
噢 Lenny跟着谁一辈子
Please.
拜托
I answered your phone, hipcrita.
我接了你的电话
It was your assistant.
是你的助理
I asked him if he canceled the flight to Milan. He said he did.
我问他能否取消去米兰的航班 他说他已经取消了
Before we even came here.
而且是在我们来之前!
He said that? Why would he say that? I mean...
他这么说的？他怎么能这么说？ 我是说...
So he just made that up, huh?
所以是他骗人了?
I'm not saying he made it up.
我可没说他骗人
I'm think... In his head he believes it's true.
大概是他臆想出来的
Don't you agent me, Lenny.
别想忽悠我 Lenny
Stop trying to handle everybody and everything...
学会尊重别人
...and start taking a little responsibility for once.
别总是对别人指手画脚好吗?
I'll take responsibility. Okay? You're right.
我承担责任好吗? 你是对的
I thought it would be better for our family to be here with normal people...
我觉得与其去米兰
...instead of going to Milan.
还不如和正常人一起待在这
We're normal?
我们很正常?
I was scared to tell you. It was easier for me to keep it a secret.
我不敢告诉你 藏着掖着比较容易
You peel back any marriage, there are secrets.
任何婚姻都藏着秘密
Mine is I love you. I love you very much.
我的秘密就是 我爱你至深
Roxanne, I just... I...
Roxanne  我只想说
Our kids are becoming nutty, snotty, spoiled...
孩子们 任性 骄纵惯了
- We got a nanny, we got... - So she is a nanny.
- 我们还请了保姆 - 她果然是保姆
No, no, no. She's not a nanny.
不不  她并不是保姆
Of course she's a nanny.
她就是个保姆
When does the lying stop?
啥时才能诚实点?
It stops right after this.
等这事儿办完
She's more of an au pair. Not a nanny.
她更是个互惠生 不是简单的保姆
Lenny.
Lenny
All right. That's it. The lying stops now.
好 好 自此以后 诚恳待人
I won't lie to you ever again. I swear to God.
我发誓再也不骗你了
I love you.
我爱你
Men lie.
是男人就会说谎
They can't help themselves.
狗改不了吃屎
Kurt sure as hell lies.
Kurt也肯定说谎了
What do I lie about, Toe-J Simpson?
我说什么谎了 脚丹妈妈?
Oh, please. The nanny.
拜托 保姆的事儿吧
What about the nanny?
保姆怎么了？
You have a thing for her.
你跟她有一腿
I do not have a thing for the nanny. I'm a married man. Period.
我可没偷腥! 我可是有妇之夫
But did I enjoy a nice conversation with a woman that wasn't going...
可是我的确喜欢和 不会胡言乱语 喋喋不休16:39 2010-10-11的
..."Where's this?" and "Did you pick up that?" Yeah.
女士聊天
What, you can have nice conversations with me.
我们可以好好说话的啊
When? You're always working.
你不总是忙吗?
And when you come home, you're just tired all the time.
一到家就喊累
You barely even touch me or look at me.
懒得看我一下 更不会碰我
He sounds like an old woman.
他说话像个老娘们似的
Deanne, you should have married Umberto Denunzio like I told you.
正如我所说 Deanne 你应该嫁给Umberto Denunzio
And if I had stayed with him you'd be the one that's pregnant now, Mama.
要是我跟了他 现在就该你挺着个大肚皮了 妈妈
You probably right, sweetheart.
想来如此 甜心
I'll just butt out.
我不狗拿耗子了
Thank you.
不胜感激
Look, maybe I do take you for granted, and I'm sorry.
也许我确实不够重视你 我道歉
How's about I take you out every Thursday night for date night.
以后 每周四晚我们都 出去甜蜜一下如何?
No, Thursday's Grey's Anatomy, but any other night would be beautiful.
周四要播"实习医生格蕾" 其他晚上都可以
And as long as we're all being honest, I think I should be honest too.
大家都坦白了 我也不能再隐瞒
I'm actually not a part owner of the lawn furniture store.
我其实不是什么草坪家具店合伙人
I don't even work there anymore.
我都不在那儿混饭吃了
I got laid off in April.
我四月份就卷铺盖了
But I rented the Caddy...
我租下凯迪拉克
...and I acted like a big shot because I didn't want you guys to know.
扮个大款 就是不想让你们知道
Lamonsoff.
Lamonsoff
You don't have to hide anything from us. I'm sorry.
你没必要瞒着我们啊 我很难过
Yeah. Since we're getting things off our chests here...
既然大家都敞开心扉
...I got a confession to make.
我也准备坦诚相待
I'm wearing a toup.
我戴着假发
No shit.
果然这么蠢
I have a confession to make.
我也要坦白
I'm really a man.
我其实是个男的
- No. - I said that.
- 不是吧 - 我就说吧
- Are you kidding? - No, I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding.
- 不会吧? - 我开玩笑的
I'm really a little hurt that so many of you believed it.
你们竟然会相信 太伤心了
- We were just saying that... - You're very womanly.
- 说说罢了 - 你很有女人味
Nevertheless. I know it's not my place, but...
不过 虽然这不是我的地盘
Well, after all, I am older than anyone here.
但是长者为尊
Hell, yeah, you are.
不错 您是长者
Well, despite the joking and the razzing, I see a lot of love here.
这里虽然又吵又闹 但也很有爱
And with love comes hostility.
而有了爱 就会有恨
Like Rob when he snapped at me the other day.
比如说 Rob那天冲我发飙
That was scary.
很吓人的
And you all thought that I was so calm, but inside?
我虽表面淡定
Inside I was saying:
可是内心却在说
"Gloria Noonan...
Gloria Noonan
...do not call him a bug-eyed sociopath with a little-man complex.
别骂他青蛙眼反社会小男人
Do not say that his hair makes him look like a dirty Q-tip."
别数落他的头发像根掏耳屎的棉棒
I like that.
此言得之
"Or that he resembles an elder gay Jonas brother."
或者笑他看起来像一个垂暮的玻璃
They get it. They get the point of where you're going.
够了 他们明白了
"Or a midget Filipino Fonzie." I didn't say those things.
或者侏儒矮人什么的... 我都忍住了
- That's my favorite one. - Hey.
- 正是如此 - 嘿
Toupee.
假发哥
Life can be difficult sometimes.
生活充满艰辛
It gets bumpy, what with family and kids...
道路崎岖不平 家庭 孩子...
...and things not going exactly like you planned.
并非万事如意
But that's what makes it interesting.
可正是因为这样才妙趣横生
In life, the first act, always exciting.
生活 首先都是迷恋激情
The second act...
接着的才是
...that's where the depth comes in.
深度的思考
Why didn't you ever tell us that she gets it?
你怎么不告诉我们 她如此有深度
Yeah, you were holding out.
对 你瞒着我们呢
That's what I've been trying to tell you guys.
我一直在努力告诉你们
That was beautiful, honey. That was beautiful.
棒极了 宝贝 棒极了
Group hug.
一起拥抱吧
Okay, it's in position.
好了 就在这
I don't know, man. This thing looks crazy.
我不知道 秀逗了吧
It'll be fun. I spent all morning blowing that thing up.
很好玩的! 我用了一早上才把它吹好
You should be all right.
你应该会没事的
- Should be? - Yeah.
- 应该? - 嗯
Ready?
准备好没?
Go.
跳
Let's do that again.
哥还要再爽一下!
It's not a favor. It's like a great investment for me, man.
这不只是小忙 这可是为我投资
A car detailing center.
汽车美容中心
And there's none around, it's gonna be a goldmine.
周围仅此一家 肯定财源广进
I don't wanna take your money.
我不想要你的钱
- You're making me more. - I want in, okay?
- 你在帮我赚钱 - 我也加入 行不？
I know the owner of the Celtics. And I can get us that account.
我认识凯尔特人队的老板 我能拿下他
Those guys all drive Bentleys and Ferraris.
那些家伙可都是开宾利和法拉利的
How do you know the owner of the Celtics?
你怎么认识凯尔特人的老板的?
Hey, I'm the leader of his daughter's Girl Scout troop.
我是他女儿所在童子军的掌门人
If he wants to make sure she gets her Cookie Biz badge...
如果他关心女儿的Cookie Biz奖章
...he will give us that account.
他就会跟我签单的
- I love you guys. - I love it. I love it.
- 我爱你们 - 不错 不错
You ready to have some fun?
准备好找乐子了吗？
Yeah. Hit it.
来吧
Okay.
没事
Go. Go. You gotta get it in high.
来啊  来啊  你肯定会爽翻!
You really wanna do this, Bailey?
Bailey 你真想这样？
My five against your five.
我们五个对你们五个
Oh, boy, look at this.
嘿 看看吧
I see the boys stayed in shape, huh?
身材保持得不错啊?
Robideaux, good to see you.
Robideaux 见到你真高兴
Lenny.
Lenny
If you're looking at me, I don't know.
你在看我吗? 我不知道呢
Look, we just wanna eat watermelon and relax, if you're all right with that.
我们只想吃点西瓜 放松下 算了吧
Oh, no. It's not all right. You're not gonna weasel out of this one, Feder.
不能算 你这次躲不掉的 Feder
Wiley snuck out of intensive care to see you finally get some justice.
Wiley都特意逃出来看你出洋相了
Yo. You best be getting to balling, Feder.
嘿 准备好屁滚尿流吧 Feder
Oh, hey, Wiley. Was the field goal good?
嘿 Wiley 你的篮投进了吗?
Yeah. First time I ever heard that one.
得了 这玩笑我可是头一回听到
Okay. Sorry, man.
啊 对不住
Do you want me to get something off the top shelf? Heard that one a lot too.
要我从天花板上取东西吗? 这个我倒是经常听到
Seriously, Dickie, let us just hang out with our families. We wanna relax.
说真的 Dickei 我是来和家人 放松的
Yeah. They're afraid of us. That's what it is.
怕了吧 我看你是怕了
We're afraid you might eat the ball before we even start the game.
怕球还没开始打 就被你们先吃了
Same old Higgins. He can talk the talk but he can't...
Higgins 没变啊 就嘴皮子厉害 但他不能...
I forget the rest.
后面是什么来着
We got Rob here with the bad foot. You can't do it, right, buddy?
Rob瘸了 你打不了球的 对吗?
I think if the Buzzer was here, he'd want me to try.
要是教练在这儿 他肯定会让我试试
I think he'd want us all to try.
他会让我们都上的
Was that William Shatner?
这是小马哥吗?
- All right, let's do this, then. - It's on.
- 成 谁怕谁 - 大战在即!
Game to 21.
21分胜
Hey, hey. Okay, come on.
嘿嘿 一起啊
Guys! Look!
大家快看!
Well, well, well, if it isn't the other black guy who grew up here.
呵呵 这不是在这长大的黑小二嘛
No, no, no. In this town, I'm the black guy and you're the other black guy.
呵呵 我可是这的黑老大 你才是小二
No, man, in this town, I'm the black guy.
呵呵 我才是黑老大
White people see me coming in their store, they get scared.
如果我进小白的店子 他们会吓得六神无主
Yeah? When white people see me coming into their store, they run.
如果我进店子 他们会魂飞魄散
Yeah, yeah. These my white people. Go get your own.
这些是我的小白 找你自己的去
You crazy, man.
你秀逗了吧
Lucky shot.
运气罢了
Defense, defense, defense.
守住 守住 守住
In your face.
咄咄逼人!
Hey, guys. Motion '78.
伙计们 按78年那次打
To me, man.
传给我
Show me what you got. Say what?
有什么大招快亮出来啊
Hey, Y! Where's M-C-A?
Y哥 M姐 C妹 和 A弟哪儿去了?
What the hell is that? Sounds like owls having sex.
什么情况 猫头鹰在做爱?
Robideaux, heads up.
Robideaux 小心!
- What are you doing? - I'm sorry! I'm sorry! Did that go in?
- 你在干嘛? - 承让了哈
You made me spill my freaking beer.
你弄撒了我的啤酒!
Honey, why does everything always have to be about you?
亲爱的 为什么你总爱抱怨?
Why do you always have to be such a dink?
你为什么总惹我抱怨?
Get that. Yeah, yeah, right there.
接球 接球 对了
I can't do this anymore.
跑不动了
I can't even breathe.
胸闷气喘的
I haven't felt my legs since the second quarter.
第二节我腿就麻了
Hey, you wanna fake injuries?
你想装受伤吗?
- You got it. - Okay.
- 好吧
- Oh, my... - Oh, God!
- 额滴神 - 额滴仙
I can't go on. I got a slippery disk.
我扭了脚 撑不住了
Oh, hon.
哦 亲爱的
- Oh, it just slipped out. - I'm done.
- 我扭了 - 不行了
Somebody's gonna have a heart attack.
有人会心脏病发的
What are you doing?
搞什么飞机?
That's it?
完了?
Darth Vader, let's go. Sit down.
Darth Vader 坐下吧
Please, honey.
加油 亲爱的
Is that a cannoli from Virgilio's?
Virgilio的奶油甜卷?
Did you seriously just take your daughter's cannoli?
你居然和女儿抢东西吃?
It's from Virgilio's. Leave me alone.
忍不住啊 这可是Virgilio的
Don't choke, Daddy.
别噎着了 爸爸
What do you say we bring my son and your son into this?
我们父子对你们父子 如何?
- Done. - Greggie.
- 成 - Greggie
- Me? - Yeah. Go, Greg.
- 我? - 太好了 上啊
Come on, baby. You can do this.
上啊 宝贝儿 你行的
Hey, Bailey.
嘿 Bailey
Somebody fill up that jug with some Boss water, for the Hollywood kid.
给好莱坞的公子准备点喝的吧 比如 Boss水
It's Voss, with a V.
是 Voss 胜利的V
Would you mind if I touch your belly? I love babies. I love to feel them kick.
嘿 能摸下肚皮不? 我很爱宝宝 喜欢被他们踢
- Yeah, go ahead. - Oh, thank you.
- 好 摸吧 - 谢谢你
That's not my baby, that's my boob.
这不是孩子 这是孩子的饭
- Oh, I like to feel those too. - Hey.
- 这货我也喜欢 - 嘿
Hey, no harm done.
没人受伤害的
- All right, take it out. Come on. - Sixteen to 16.
- 精神点 - 16比16
Half court, two on two. Let's go.
半场 二对二
Keep your feet off the line this time.
这回可别踩线了
It's tied score. Tied score. Let's see something. Nice throw.
平局了 来点真家伙 好球
Tied score, guys.
平局了
All right, son. All right.
好吧 小家伙
- We're up 19-16. Let's go. - All right, son. Give me the ball.
- 19比16  我们领先了 - 好吧 孩子 传球给我
- Come on, son. - That's it, Greg. You can do it.
- 加油 儿子 - 没错 Greg 就这么打
You know what's going on.
你知道怎么打的
Oh, yes. It's raining threes on Hollywood.
好莱坞满天都是三分球!
His foot was on the line. Your foot was on the line.
他脚踩线了 你脚踩线了
It ain't raining threes.
可没有什么满天飞的三分球
- It's drizzling twos! - That's all right. Good shot.
- 飞的两分球! - 算了算了 好球
- Wasn't no three. Foot was on the line. - Next basket wins. Let's go.
- 那不是三分 他踩了线 - 再投一个就赢了 加油
Come on.
加油
This is it, pal.
就是这样 兄弟
Take him out, baby.
干掉他
All right, all right, all right. Take him, baby. Take him.
就是这样 就是这样 干掉他
Pop it, Lenny.
投了  Lenny
Bank's open, Dad.
爸爸 标准篮板
He never misses that shot.
他从没失过手
Down goes Hollywood.
好莱坞输了
We'll crush them next year. I'll work on my left when we get back to L.A.
等我回洛杉矶练好左手 明年再搞定他们
- That's my boy. I love you. - I love you too.
- 这才是我儿子 我爱你 - 我也爱你
You're awesome.
你很不错
- Way to go! - We did it!
- 我们赢了! - 成功了!
Hey, Lenny.
嘿 Lenny
I thought you never missed a bank shot.
我以为你标准篮板百发百中呢
Yeah. Well, I just thought...
是啊 可是我觉得
...the Baileys needed to learn how to win every once in a while...
Bailey家人偶尔需要学会拥有
...and Feders needed to learn how to lose.
而Feder家人需要学会放弃
- That was nice. - Yeah?
- 你很体贴 - 是啊
I'm proud of you.
为你骄傲
Look at these guys.
看看他们
- Lenny. Hey, man. - Yeah, buddy.
- 嘿 Lenny - 嘿 哥们儿
I know you're bummed about losing the game for us.
我知道你为我们输了球很难过
And you're drunk?
你醉了?
- No. Yes. - Oh, okay.
- 没有 - 好吧
Hey, man, there's one thing they'll never beat us at.
有件事他们怎么都赢不了
What's this?
什么事?
Arrow roulette, baby.
神箭大轮盘
- We are good at that. - Yeah.
- 我们都很擅长 - 正是如此
- All right. - What are you doing?
- 嘿 大伙儿 - 你要干嘛?
- Last one to stay in wins. - No, no, no.
- 最后没跑的就赢 - 别 别 别
Becky.
Becky
Run away. Not again.
快跑 又来了
Get out of my way.
滚开
Little help here? Take me with you?
谁来帮帮Y哥 扛我走啊
Seriously, you're gonna leave me?
你们真的见死不救?
No.
不要
We win again.
我们又赢了